墨西哥  伊斯坦科
尼克  这是很悲剧  但我们不是为此而来
Nick, this was a tragedy, but it's not why we're here.
我们现在还负责对抗天气了吗
What, are we fighting the weather now?
本地人说龙卷风长了脸
Locals say the cyclone had a face.
人在高压下是可能出现幻觉的
People see things when they're under stress.
那不代表这又是什么
Okay? That does not mean that this is the start
重大的世界末日...
to some other big world-ending--
你们是谁
Who are you?
你们不想掺和进来的
You don't want any part of this.
我
And I...
将永远爱你
Will always love you, ooh
永远爱你
Will always love you
你
You
我亲爱的你
My darling, you...
苦甜参半
Bittersweet
那些回忆
Memories
那就是
That is all
缅怀
我能
I'm taking
带走的一切
With me
我
And I
将永远爱你
Will always love you
我永远
I will always
爱你
Love you
我永远
I, I will always
爱你
Love you
英雄已逝  永不遗忘
Gone, but not forgotten.
感谢基纳斯·林和维翰·拉玛莫斯
Thanks to Kenneth Lim and Vihaan Ramamurthy
剪辑了这段感人的致敬视频
for their help with that touching video tribute.
今年可以说是...
This year has been nothing short of--
杰森·艾乃罗  贝蒂·布兰特
疯狂  简直太疯狂了
...is crazy. It's, like, insane.
-杰森  -怎么了
- Jason. - What?
不许说脏话
No swearing.
反正明天放假了  没事的
Yeah. It's the last day of school. We're good.
历史性
Historic.
五年多前
Over five years ago,
全宇宙一半的生命
half of all life in the universe,
也包括我们城中高中的一半生命
including our own Midtown High...
都被抹去了
...was wiped from existence.
但八个月前
But then eight months ago,
一群勇敢的英雄把我们带了回来
a band of brave heroes brought us back.
此事件被称为"闪烁"
They called it "The Blip."
我们这些闪灭了的人  以原年龄回归了
Those of us who Blipped away came back the same age...
苏·罗曼  五年前
苏·罗曼  今日
但我们没有闪灭的同学们
But our classmates that didn't Blip
布拉德·戴维斯  五年前
则长大了五岁
had grown five years older.
布拉德·戴维斯  今日
是啊  我弟弟现在比我大了
Yeah, like my little brother is now older than me.
是啊  这是数学
Yeah, it's math.
尽管我们闪灭时  学年已过去了一半
And even though we had Blipped away halfway through the school year
而且已经考过期中考了
and had already taken midterms,
学校还是要求我们从头重上这个学年
the school made us start the year over from the beginning.
太不公平了  这不对
It's totally unfair. It's not right.
城中虎们
Tigers...
这段旅程漫长  戏剧性
...it's been a long, dramatic,
而且还有些令人困惑
somewhat confusing road.
随着今年即将结束
As we draw this year to a close,
我们也该向前看了
it's time to move on...
迎来我们生命的新阶段
to a new phase of our lives.
祈祷不会再发生什么疯狂事
Pray nothing crazy happens again
因为现在还有复仇者联盟吗
because are the Avengers even like a thing anymore?
有人有什么计划吗
Does anyone even have a plan?
我有个计划
I have a plan.
首先  我要在飞机上挨着MJ坐
Okay. First, I'm gonna sit next to MJ on the flight.
第二  我要买个双耳机插口
Second, I'm gonna buy a dual headphone adapter
跟她看一路的电影
and watch movies with her the whole time.
-好  -第三
- Okay. - Three,
等我们到了威尼斯
when we go to Venice,
那里的玻璃制品非常有名  是吧
Venice is super famous for making stuff out of glass right?
-对  -所以我要给她买条黑色大丽花项链
- True. - So, I'm gonna buy her a black dahlia necklace
因为她最喜欢的花就是黑色大丽花
because her favorite flower is the black dahlia
-因为...  -那起谋杀
- because of, well... - The murder.
没错  第四  等我们到了巴黎
The murder. Four, when we go to Paris,
我要带她登上埃菲尔铁塔顶部
I'm gonna take her to the top of the Eiffel Tower,
把项链送她
give her the necklace.
然后  第五  我要向她表白
And then, five, I'm gonna tell her how I feel.
然后  第六  希望她会说
And then, six, hopefully she tells me
她对我也有一样的感觉
she feels the same way.
别忘了第七步
Oh, don't forget step seven.
-第七步  -以上都别做
- Step Seven. - Don't do any of that.
为什么
Why?
因为我们将在欧洲做单身汉  彼得
Because, we're gonna be bachelors in Europe, Peter.
-内德  -听着
- Ned. - Look,
别的我不知道  但我知道这个
I may not know much, but I do know this:
欧洲人爱美国人
Europeans love Americans.
-是吗  -而且半数欧洲人是女人
- Really? - More than half are women.
好吧  行
Okay. Sure.
但...我真的很喜欢MJ  好吗
But... I really like MJ, man, okay?
她很棒  有种很黑暗的幽默感
She's awesome, she's super funny in a kind of dark way.
有时我还会逮到她看我
And sometimes I catch her looking at me,
我觉得我已错过...
and I feel like I've stood up...
-她来了  别说话...  -好啊  呆子们
- She's coming. Just don't say any... - What up, dorks?
期待科学出游吗
Excited about the science trip?
当然  我们正聊出游的事呢
Hey, yeah. We're just talking about the trip.
是啊  还有彼得的计划
Yeah, and Peter's plan.
你还有计划
You have a plan?
我没有什么计划
I don't... I don't have a plan.
他打算在我们周游各国期间
He's... He's just gonna collect tiny spoons
收集各种小勺子
when we're traveling to other countries.
像个老太太那样吗
Like a... Like a grandmother?
我没打算收集小勺子
I'm not collecting tiny spoons.
他才收集小勺子呢
He's collecting tiny spoons.
好吧
Okay, well...
真是跌宕起伏
that was a real roller coaster.
对了  出游建议
By the way, travel tip:
你应该在手机上下载个VPN
You should prabably download a VPN on your phone,
这样我们在国外期间  政府就无法追踪你了
just so that the government can't track you while abroad.
明智
Smart...
我一定照做
Will do.
哥们  刚刚真的很顺利
Dude, I think that went really great.
无家可归帮助组织  食物  住所  希望
我闪现回我公寓时
When I Blipped back to my apartment,
住在那里的一家人非常不解
the family that was living there was very confused.
那家的妻子以为我是男人的情妇
The wife thought that I was a mistress.
奶奶则以为我是鬼
The grandma thought that I was a ghost.
真是一团乱
It was... It was really a mess.
谢谢大家能前来
Thank you all for coming out
帮助那些因闪烁事件流离失所的人
to support those who have been displaced by the Blip.
当然  也感谢我们的本地英雄
And, of course, thanks to our very own
蜘蛛侠
Spider-Man!
帕克女士  谢谢你请我来
Thank you, Miss Parker, for having me.
也谢谢大家请我来
And thank you, you guys, for having me.
谢谢你  蜘蛛侠
And thank you, Spider-Man.
他待会儿会再来跟大家合影拍视频
He'll be right back out to take photos and videos.
谢谢大家
Thank you!
-真不错  -太棒了
- That was amazing. - That was great.
太了不起了  我紧张死了
That was so cool. I was so nervous.
我有点僵硬  我感觉我不是很在状态
I was a little stiff. I felt like I wasn't in the pocket.
不  你很棒的
No, I thought you did great.
我倒是觉得你有点僵了
Yeah. I actually think you were a little stiff.
是啊  我也觉得
Uh, yeah, I felt that too. I felt that too.
-没事的  -好
- It's fine, it's fine, it's fine. - Okay.
-你拿到护照了吗  -嗯
- Did you get your passport? - Yeah.
-小牙膏呢  -拿了
- Mini toothpaste? - Yeah, I did.
抱歉我迟到了
Hey, sorry I'm late.
哈皮
Happy.
你真美
Oh, you look lovely.
-谢谢  你也挺帅  -谢谢
- Thanks. You too. - Thank you.
-新裙子吗  -是的
- New dress? - Yeah, yes, it is.
你蓄胡子了
It's a new beard.
我的闪烁胡子
It's my... My Blip beard.
我在闪烁期间长的
'Cause I grew it in the Blip.
闪烁胡
It's a Blip beard.
我懂了
I see. Yeah.
对了  我迟到是因为
Anyway, so, the reason I'm late is because
在办公室里找不到这个了
this was misplaced at the office.
能相信吗  这么大一张
Can you believe it? Because, it's enormous.
不是指数额  是大小
Not the amount, the size.
数额也不错  挺慷慨的
The amount's nice too. They're generous.
派珀·波茨表示很遗憾不能前来
Pepper Potts said, sorry she couldn't be here.
我要去换一下
I think I'm gonna go change the
素食意面下面的固体酒精
Sterno under the vegan lasagna.
蜘蛛侠  去握手吧
Spider-Man, go shake hands.
好的
Will do.
刚刚怎么回事
What just happened?
提醒你
Heads up,
尼克·弗瑞要给你打电话
Nick Fury's calling you.
-尼克·弗瑞要给我打电话  -对
- Nick Fury's gonna call me? - Yeah.
为什么
Why?
为什么  他可能要找你做英雄的事
Why? He probably has hero stuff for you to do.
你是个超级英雄  他会给超级英雄打电话
You're a superhero. He calls superheroes.
如果真那么重要
I mean, if it was really that important,
他或许会找别人  不是我
he'd probably call someone else, not me.
看来不是这样
Apparently not.
未知号码  是他
No caller ID. That's him.
我并不想跟尼克·弗瑞通话
I don't really wanna talk to Fury.
-接电话  -为什么
- Answer the phone. - Why?
因为如果你不接
Because, if you don't talk to him,
那他就会打给我  我不想跟他通话
I have to talk to him and I don't want to talk to him.
你为什么不想跟他通话
Why don't you want to talk to him?
因为我害怕  接电话吧
Cause, I'm scared. Just answer the phone.
-你拒接尼克·弗瑞的电话  -对
- You sent Nick Fury to voicemail? - Yeah.
你不能拒接尼克·弗瑞的电话
You don't send Nick Fury to voicemail.
听到了吗  他们在喊我
Did you heart that? They're calling me.
-我得走了  -你得跟他通话
- I gotta go. I gotta go. - You gotta talk to him.
我会打给他的  我保证  我肯定打
I'm gonna call him. I promise you, I'm gonna call him. I will.
你不能跟尼克·弗瑞玩消失
You do not ghost Nick Fury.
我保证  我会打给他的
I promise you, I'll call him.
等我出游回来的
After my trip.
喂
Yeah, hi.
不  他没跟你玩消失
No, no, he's not ghosting you.
好了  一个个问题问
Okay, one question at a time.
你是复仇者联盟的领袖了吗
Are you the head Avenger?
Are you the head Avenger now?
不  我不是
Uh, no, I'm not.
如果外星人再来  你要怎么办
If aliens come back, what are you gonna do?
有谁想问关于本社区的问题吗
Does anyone have neighborhood questions?
肖恩·温福德  《皇后区论坛报》
Sean Winford, Queens Tribune.
接过托尼·斯塔克的衣钵是什么感觉
What's it like to take over from Tony Stark?
要接替他可不容易
Those are big shoes to fill.
我...
I'mma...
我先走了  谢谢大家前来
I'm gonna go. Thanks, everyone, for coming.
未知号码
好
Okay.
饿了吗
Hungry?
真抱歉
So sorry.
我以为你能感应到呢  你不是有彼得一激灵吗
I thought that you could sense that with your Peter-tingle.
拜托别管那个叫彼得一激灵
Please do not start calling it my Peter-tingle.
怎么回事  你躲得开子弹  躲不开香蕉吗
So, what's up? You can dodge bullets but not bananas?
不  我就是很需要去度这个假
No, I just really need this vacation.
我需要休息一下
I need a break.
这是你应得的
You deserve it.
好了
Yeah.
知道吗
You know what?
你该带上你的战衣  以防万一
You should pack your suit, just in case.
我有个激灵
I have a tingle about it.
别再说"激灵"了  梅
Please stop saying "Tingle," May.
不要
No.
不  不带
No. No, I'm not.
度假咯
Yeah!
能帮我把东西抬上去吗
Can you help me get my stuff up?
-抱歉  那是我的  -没事
- Oh, sorry, that's mine. - No worries.
给我个平板
Give me a tablet.
你想值第一轮班还是第二轮
Do you want first shift or second?
我都行
I could take either.
我值第三轮班吧  我服了安眠药
Give me the third shift. I took an Ambien.
我不能一个人照顾这些孩子
I can't chaperone kids alone.
帕克
Yo, Parker.
这叫飞机
This is called an airplane.
就像你习惯坐的大巴
It's like buses you're used to,
但它会飞过穷人社区
except it flies over poor neighborhoods
而不是穿过其中
instead of driving through them.
女士
Ma'am?
他闪灭了  所以他其实是16  不是21
He Blipped, so technically, he's 16, not 21.
给我吧
I'll take that.
她撒谎  我根本不认识她
She's lying. I don't even know this girl.
MJ就这么拽  是吧
Classic MJ, right?
你知道布拉德也要来吗
Did you know Brad was coming?
好奇怪啊
It... It's so weird.
前一天他还是那个爱哭的小孩
Like, one day, he's that kid who cried
总是流鼻血
and got nosebleeds all the time,
突然  我们闪现回来
and suddenly, we Blip back,
他成了肌肉暖男
and he's totally ripped and super nice
所有姑娘都喜欢他
and all these girls are after him.
也不是所有姑娘都喜欢他
Not all the girls are after him.
不  真的是都喜欢他
No, man, they're all after him.
-是啊  -来
- Yeah. - Here.
好了  说说更重要的事
Anyway, on to more important things.
这趟航程九小时
It's a nine-hour flight.
我们可以玩一路的《野兽杀手》
We can play Beast Slayers the whole time.
你激动吗
Are you excited?
我需要你帮我坐到MJ旁边
I need your help to sit next to MJ.
不是吧
Seriously?
是的
Yes, seriously.
那我们的计划呢
What about our plan?
美国单身汉欧洲行
American bachelors in Europe.
那是你的计划  是个人计划
That's your plan. That's a solo plan.
拜托  这是我的计划
Come on, this is my plan.
拜托了
Please.
伙计们
Guys.
我们前面坐了个老太太
There's an old lady sitting in front of us
擦了好多香水
wearing a crazy amount of perfume,
有点引发彼得的过敏反应了
and it's kind of setting off Peter's allergies.
贝蒂  能不能麻烦你
You know, Betty, if you could just
跟他换个座位
switch seats with him, that would be...
他对香水过敏吗
He's allergic to perfume?
是啊  因为...
Yeah, yeah, because, um, it...
他会开始流眼泪
It makes his eyes water,
-还...  -彼得对香水过敏吗
- and he can't really... - You said, Peter has a perfume allergy?
就我的亲身经验来说
I'll tell you from experience,
香水过敏可不是小事
perfume allergies are no joke.
我这就能感觉到红疹爆发了
I can feel hives breaking out already.
MJ起来
MJ, stand up.
内德  你坐MJ这里
Ned, take MJ's spot.
MJ  你坐我这里
MJ, you take my spot.
彼得  来  别坐那儿了
Peter, come with me, let's get you out of there.
-抱歉  -扎克  塞巴斯蒂安
- Sorry. - Zach, Sebastian,
你们去坐内德和彼得的座
you take Ned and Peter's seats.
内德  谢谢你告知我此事
Ned, thanks for bringing this to my attention.
你们的安全是我的责任
Your safety is my responsibility.
也是戴尔老师的责任  但他...
And Mr. Dell's, but he's...
现在你们有我  走吧  彼得
I got it for now. Let's go, Peter!
走吧
Let's go!
我膀胱小  我坐过道
Yeah, I have a small bladder, so I took the aisle.
你想玩《野兽杀手》吗
So did you wanna play Beast Slayer?
不想
Nope.
你玩过电脑游戏吗
Have you ever played any kind of PC game or...?
-没有  -了解了
- No. - Got it.
我跟你讲过我妻子假装闪灭了吗
Did I tell you my wife pretended to Blip out?
原来  她是跟她登山队一男的跑了
Turns out, she ran off with a guy in her hiking group.
我们还为她举行了假葬礼
We had a fake funeral for her and everything.
葬礼是真的
Well, the funeral was real
因为我真以为她死了
because I thought she was dead.
你想看视频吗
Do you wanna see the video?
我带了双耳机插口
I got a dual headphone adapter
你想看电影吗
if you wanna watch a movie.
只看致郁的  或搞笑的
Only if it's depressing. Or hilarious.
你带了双耳机插口
You have a dual headphone adapter.
我们一起看吧
We can watch together.
下午好  女士们先生们
Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen,
这里是机长
this is your captain speaking.
今天的飞行时长为
Our flight time today will be
8小时49分钟  目的地是意大利威尼斯
eight hours, 49 minutes to Venice, Italy.
钢铁之心  托尼·斯塔克传
意大利  威尼斯
伙计  你看到布拉德和MJ在飞机上的样子了吗
Hey man, did you see Brad and MJ on the plane?
他们整个航程中一直在看电影  欢笑
They were watching movies and laughing the entire time.
哥们  别担心了
Dude, don't worry, okay?
肯定没什么事的
I'm sure that's nothing.
宝贝
Hey, babe.
能帮我拿一下吗
Can you hold this for me?
-当然  -谢谢
- Yeah, of course. - Thanks.
怎么回事
What was that?
这个嘛
Well,
我们在机上聊了天  原来
we acutally got to talking on the plane, and it turns out,
我们有好多共同点
we have a lot in common.
所以我们现在是男女朋友了
So, uh, we're boyfriend and girlfriend now.
不是说要做畅游欧洲的美国单身汉吗
Whatever happened to being an American bachelor in Europe?
彼得  那是少年轻狂的傻话
Peter, those were the words of a boy.
那少年认识了一个女人
And that boy met a woman.
一个强势有力的女人
A very strong and powerful woman.
现在  少年成长为男人了
And now, that boy's a man.
-宝贝  -来了  宝贝
- Babe? - Coming, babe.
里面没什么奇怪的东西  我发誓
There's nothing in there. I swear.
你差点忘了这个  梅
这个  不行
These, no.
抱歉
Sorry.
-我来了  -等等
- I'm here. - Wait, wait, wait.
-我来了  -谢天谢地
- I'm here. - Thank goodness.
看来我们到了
Looks like we're here.
他们在进行翻修
They're doing renovations to the place.
旅馆
-进行升级  -这地方好烂
- Getting some upgrades. - Oh, this is trash.
-那肯定是门房了  -好吧
- That must be the concierge. - Okay.
来吧
Come on, man.
各位  我们到了
Everyone, here we are.
进来吧
Come on in.
这地方在下沉
This place is sinking.
-是"有魅力"吧  -好臭
- You mean, "Charming." - It stinks.
各位  包放下
Okay, everybody, drop your bags off.
3点去达·芬奇博物馆见  快行动
We're gonna meet at the da Vinci Museum at 3. Let's go!
-快走吧[西语]  -是快走[意大利语]
- ¡Vámanos! - It's "Andiamo."
快走
Andiamo!
入乡随俗
When in Rome, do as Romans do.
在威尼斯  就难免沾湿袜子
When you're in Venice, your socks get wet.
好啊  弗拉粉  你们怎么样
What's up, Flash Mob? How you guys doing?
我在圣马可波罗...
I'm here in St. Marco Polo's...
-这太好玩了  -是吧
- This is so much fun. - Yeah?
三  二  一  说披萨
Three, two, one... say pizza!
披萨
Pizza!
-早上好  -早上好
- Buongiorno. - Buongiorno.
我想找...
I'm looking for a, uh...
完美
It's perfect.
什么
What?
全世界最完美的词
It's the most perfect word in the world.
意大利人发明的  被我发现了
Italians created it, and I discovered it.
什么意思
What does it mean?
这就是重点  它能有无数意义
That's the thing. It can means a million things.
能是...比如说  给我滚开的意思
I can mean... I don't know. Get out of my face.
或是  我不知道  滚开
I don't know and get out of my face.
是意大利人最伟大的发明  或许除了浓缩咖啡吧
It's the best thing Italy created, except for maybe espresso.
你喝浓缩咖啡了
Oh, so you've been drinking espresso?
德国人  美国人
German? American.
买朵玫瑰吧
A rose for you.
这是我的新超能力了
"Boh" is my new superpower.
就像"你好"[夏威夷语]的反义词
It's like the anti-"Aloha."
我注定要说这个词
I was born to say this word.
包里是什么
So, what's in the bag?
真行
Nice.
酷
Whoa, cool.
那是怎么回事
What was that?
-贝蒂  你没事吧  -嗯
- Betty! You okay? - Yeah.
-天啊  -快来
- Oh, my God! - Come on.
伙计们  我们得走了
Guys, we gotta go!
-那是什么  -我不知道
- What is that? - I don't know.
-你要怎么办  -我把战衣留在旅馆了
- What'll you do? - I left my suit's in the hotel room.
-为什么  -我在度假  内德
- Why? - I'm on vacation, Ned!
大家会看到我的脸的  快带他们走
Everyone's gonna see my face. Just get them out.
-走  快走  -快走
- Go! Just go! - Go!
快走  走
Get out of here. Go!
天啊
Oh, my God.
好吧
Come on.
别想
Oh, no, you don't.
没事吧  快走
You okay? Get out of here. Go!
不好意思  先生
Excuse me, sir!
我可以帮忙  让我帮忙吧
I... I can help. Let me help.
我很强壮  还很黏
I'm really strong, and I'm sticky.
我需要把它引离运河
I need to lead it away from the canals.
达·芬奇博物馆
The da Vinci Museum.
我们就是为此来威尼斯
This is why we're here in Venice.
就是这里
Oh, this is it.
闭馆了
It's closed.
什么叫闭馆了  到什么时候
What do you mean it's closed? Till when?
11月
November.
你没查看网站吗
You didn't check the website?
这是个好想法
Oh, that's a good idea.
不是吧
Oh, come on.
趴下  孩子们  这里安全的
Stay low, kids. We'll be safe here.
那人是谁
Who is that guy?
我不知道  但那水怪被他打得很惨
I don't know, but he's kicking that water's ass.
好样的
Yeah! Yeah!
是外星人  肯定是
It's aliens. It has to be.
消息网说有个水手  莫里斯·本奇
BuzzFeed says there's a sailor, name Morris Bench,
因接触实验性水下发电机
who was exposed to an experimental underwater generator
而获得了水超能力
and got hydro powers.
是啊  你是该相信
Yeah, you should definitely believe
在网上读到的一切
everything you read on the Internet.
-蜘蛛侠能打得过他  -你觉得是什么
- Spider-Man could take him. - What do you think it is?
作为一个相信科学的人
You know, being a man of science...
巫术
witches.
不不不  我们想留下
No, no, no. We wanna stay. We wanna stay.
幸好我给你带上了战衣  是吧
It's a good thing that I packed your suit, huh?
你居然给忘了
I can't believe you forgot it.
是啊
Yeah.
跟你一起作战的那人是谁
So, who was that guy that you were with?
那是斯特兰奇先生吗
Was that Mr. Strange?
是斯特兰奇博士  梅
Doctor Strange, May. Doctor Strange.
不  我不知道那是谁
And, no, I don't know who that was.
是个新来的
It was a new guy.
-我想帮他  但...  -哈皮
- I was trying to help him, but... - Happy,
那是我的午餐
that's my lunch.
别吃那个
Don't eat that one.
哈皮也在吗
Happy's there?
对  是哈皮
Yeah, it's Happy.
他在这儿  来做志工
He's here. He came by to volunteer.
顺便来办公室看看
And he's hanging around the office.
-他想跟你打个招呼  -我不想...彼得
- And he wants to say hi. - I don't want... Hi, Peter.
哈皮
Hey, Happy.
抱歉  我忙呢  我得送个传单
Sorry, I'm working hard here. I gotta do a... A leaflet drop.
-你在干什么...  -很高兴你玩得开心
- What are you doing in...? - Glad you're having a good time.
别担心  我会照顾好你婶婶
Don't worry, I'm really taking care of your aunt.
你的计划怎么样了
So how's the plan going?
是遭遇了些挫折
There's been setbacks, for sure.
别想太多  相信直觉就好
Don't over think it, just trust your instincts, you'll be fine.
我知道  爱你  再见
I know. Love you. Bye.
那人是谁
Who is that guy?
他就像钢铁侠和托尔的集合体
He's Iron Man and Thor rolled into one.
他还行吧  他可不比蜘蛛侠
He's all right. He's no Spider-Man.
你为什么这么痴迷于蜘蛛侠
What is it with you and Spider-Man?
怎么了  他很赞的
What? He's just awesome, okay?
他保护本地社区  很激励人
He protects the neighborhood and, you know, he's inspiring.
他激励我做个更好的人
He inspires me to be a better man.
好啊  蠢蛋
What's up, dickwad?
我以为你淹死了
Thought you drowned.
看来他名叫神秘客
Sounds like his name's Mysterio.
那句话
"L'uomo del misterio"
是意大利语  "神秘男子"
is Italian for "Man of mystery."
他们并不清楚他的身份
They don't actually know who he is.
神秘客
Mysterio.
名字不错
Cool name.
宝贝
Babe.
你看到了多少
So how much of that did you actually see?
没看到多少  我忙着跑呢
Not much. I was running.
是啊  我也是  我也忙着跑呢
Right. Me too. I was also running...
跑远
away.
明天去巴黎了
So Paris tomorrow.
去埃菲尔铁塔
Go to the Eiffel Tower.
应该很棒
Should be great.
我读到它建造的秘密目的是作为头脑控制天线
Yeah, I read it was secretly built as a mind control antenna
以制造疯子大军
to create an army of the insane.
所以那里是我整个出游最喜欢的目的地
Which is why it's my favorite destination on the whole trip.
你要怎么对付那个水怪
What are you gonna do about the water monster?
不做什么  它死了
Nothing. It's dead.
再说  那个神秘客都搞定了
Besides, that Mysterio guy's all over it.
我只想跟MJ一起玩玩
Look, I just wanna spend time with MJ.
我们刚刚聊起巴黎  我觉得她是喜欢我的
We were talking about Paris, and I think she really likes me.
真不错
That's nice.
让我想起了我和贝蒂刚相爱时
Reminds me of when Betty and I first fell in love.
我刚吃完我的水果馅饼
I had just finished my fruit cobbler, and...
联系你可真不容易  蜘蛛侠
You're a very difficult person to contact, Spider-Man.
你是尼克·弗瑞
You're Nick Fury.
你射晕了内德
And you just shot Ned.
只是温和的麻醉剂
Just a mild tranquilizer.
他不会有事的
He'll be all right.
很高兴终于见到你了
So good to finally meet you.
我在葬礼上看到你了
I saw you at the funeral,
但我觉得当时不是交换号码的好时机
but I didn't think that was a good time to exchange numbers.
是啊  那就太不合适了
No, that would've been really inappropriate.
-我不就这么说的吗  -是啊
- That's what I just said. - Right.
重要的是  你到这儿了
The important thing is, you're here.
我本想叫你来的
I tried to bring you here.
但你躲我  可现在你还是来了
You avoided me, and now you're here.
真巧
What a coincidence.
等等  这是巧合吗
Wait. Was this a coincidence?
我以前无所不知
I used to know everything.
然后我消失了五年再回来
Then I come back five years later,
现在我什么都不知道了
and now I know nothing.
没有情报  没有团队
No intel, no team.
一个高中小子
And a high school kid
都敢不接我电话
is dodging my calls.
我知道的是
Here's what I do know:
一周前  墨西哥一村庄被一场龙卷风摧毁
A week ago, a village in Mexico was wiped out by a cyclone.
目击者说  那龙卷风长了脸
Witnesses say that cyclone had a face.
三天后  摩洛哥发生类似事件
Three days later, a similar event in Morocco.
一个村庄...
A village was...
来查个房
Just making the rounds.
看看经历了今天的创伤性事件
See if anyone needs any emotional counseling
是否有人需要情感咨询
after today's traumatic events.
不  我们没事的  谢谢
No, we'll be okay. We're fine. Thank you.
很好  因为我其实没资格做...
Great because I'm... I'm not qualified to actually...
他睡熟了
Oh, he's passed out.
我反正也没那个资质  晚安了
I'm really not qualified to do it anyway, so good night.
那是我老师  抱歉了
That was my teacher. Sorry about that.
你刚刚在说
You were saying?
一个村庄被摧毁
A village was destroyed by
这可能又是一个威胁世界的...
what may well be another world-threatening...
宝贝  你还醒着吗
Babe, you still awake?
你不回我短信
You're not answering any of my texts.
他睡着了  贝蒂
He's asleep, Betty.
这么早
Oh, already?
-是啊  -好吧
- Yeah. - Okay.
所以  我们务必...
That's why it's imperative...
孩子们  今天那运河的水
Boys. So that canal water today
充满了危险的细菌
was filled with dangerous bacteria...
再有人来敲门
Another person touches that door,
你和我就又要参加一场葬礼了
you and I are going to attend another funeral.
穿战衣
Suit up.
如果你们俩有谁开始呕吐要告诉我
Let me know if either of you develop vomiting.
斯塔克把这个留给了你
Stark left these for you.
是吗
Really?
"欲戴王冠  必承其重"
"Uneasy lies the head that wears the crown."
斯塔克说你不会懂的
Stark said you wouldn't get that
因为不是《星战》梗
because it's not a Star Wars reference.
摘了面罩吧
You can lose the mask.
这里的人都见过你的真身
Everyone here has seen you without it.
你只是无故
You'd only be feigning anonymity
装神秘  还要隔着布料呼吸
and breathing through spandex for no good reason.
走吧
Come on.
好
Yeah.
那是玛丽亚·希尔
Over there, we have Maria Hill.
这是德米崔
That is Dimitri.
这是贝克先生
And this is Mr. Beck.
神秘客
Mysterio?
什么
What?
没什么
Doesn't matter.
我朋友这么喊你
It's what my friends have been calling you.
你可以喊我昆廷
Well, you can call me Quentin.
你今天的表现真出色
You handled yourself well out there today.
我看到你拉着那座塔楼了
I saw what you did with the tower.
我的世界就需要你这种人
We could use someone like you on my world.
谢谢
Thanks.
什么  你的世界
I'm sorry. Your world?
贝克先生是来自地球
Mr. Beck is from Earth.
但不是你的地球
Just not yours.
现实有很多个  彼得
There are multiple realities, Peter.
这里是616号地球  我来自833号地球
This is Earth Dimension 616. I'm from Earth 833.
抱歉  你是说存在多元宇宙吗
I'm sorry, you're saying there's a multiverse?
我以为那只是个理论
'Cause I thought that was just theoretical.
这将完全改变
I mean, that completely changes
我们对初始奇点的理解
how we understand the initial singularity.
这可是个永恒膨胀的系统
We're talking about an eternal inflation system.
那怎么行得通  那么多量...
How does that even work with all the quantum...?
真是疯了
It's insane.
抱歉  好酷啊
S-sorry. It's really cool.
不要为比其他人聪明而道歉
Don't ever apologize for being the smartest one in the room.
好了
Anyway...
它们诞生于黑洞中的稳定轨道
They were born in stable orbits within black holes.
是基本元素构成的生灵
Creatures formed from the primary elements:
气  水  火  土
Air, water, fire, earth.
科学部为它们起了学名
The Science Division had a technical name.
但我们喊它们元素怪
We just called them Elementals.
它们的变体普版存在于我们的神话中
Versions of them exist across our mythologies.
原来传说都是真的
Turns out, the myths are real.
就像托尔
Like Thor.
托尔原是传说  但现在是我物理课的内容
Thor was a myth, and now I study him in my physics class.
这些传说是威胁
These myths are threats.
它们最初于多年前在我的地球上实体化
They first materialized on my Earth many years ago.
我们调动力量与它们交手
We mobilized and fought them,
但它们随着每场战斗愈发强大
but with each battle, they grew, got stronger.
我是仅剩的最后一支阻止它们的军团的一员
I was part of the last battalion left trying to stop them.
但我们只推迟了不可避免的结局
All we did was delay the inevitable.
元素怪又来到了这里  袭击相同的地点
The Elementals are here now, attacking the same coordinates.
卫星已证实了这点
Our satellites confirm it.
所以感谢贝克先生摧毁了另三个
So thank Mr. Beck for destroying the other three.
现在只剩一个了  火
There's only one left: fire.
它们中最强的一个
The strongest of them all.
摧毁了我的地球的那个
The one that destroyed my Earth.
也是杀死我家人的那个
It's the one that took my family.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
再过大概48小时  它就会出现在布拉格
And it will be in Prague in approximately 48 hours.
我们只有一项任务  干掉它
We have one mission: kill it.
你要跟我们一起来
And you're coming with us.
抱歉  你是说布拉格吗
I'm sorry, did you say Prague?
弗瑞先生  这似乎是很严重的事
Mr. Fury, this all seems like bigtime,
很重大的  超级英雄的那种事
you know, huge superhero kind of stuff.
我只是友好邻居蜘蛛侠  先生
And, I mean, I'm just a friendly neighborhood Spider-Man, sir.
少来了  你上过太空呢
Bitch, please. You've been to space.
我知道  但那是意外
I know, but that was an accident.
先生  拜托  你肯定还能找别人吧
Sir, come on. There's gotta be someone else you can use.
-托尔呢  -去别的世界了
- What about Thor? - Off-world.
好吧  斯特兰奇博士
Okay, um, Doctor Strange.
-没空  -惊奇队长
- Unavailable. - Captain Marvel.
别跟我提她
Don't invoke her name.
先生  我真的想帮忙的
Sir, look, I really wanna help. I do.
但如果我婶婶得知我离开了大部队
But if my aunt finds out I left my class trip,
她会杀了我的
she's gonna kill me.
经过了华盛顿纪念堂的事
And if I'm seen like this in Europe
如果我再这样在欧洲出现
after the Washington Monument,
我全班同学都会猜到我的身份
my whole class will figure out who I am, and then...
那全世界就都知道我的身份了
Then the whole world will figure out who I am,
我就完了
then I'm done.
好吧
Okay.
我理解
I understand.
抱歉  什么
I'm sorry, what?
你快回去吧  别被老师发现你不见了
Why don't you get back before your teachers miss you
起了疑心
and become suspicious.
德米崔
Dimitri.
带他回旅馆去
Take him back to the hotel, please.
好
Yes.
谢谢  弗瑞先生
Thank you, Mr. Fury.
祝你们好运
And, uh, good luck.
回见  孩子
See you, kid.
好  回见
Yeah, see you.
-再见  女士  -嗯
- Bye, ma'am. - Yeah.
好  多喝水
Okay, drink lots of water.
我给你找维C片剂
I'm gonna get you a vitamin C pill.
你可不能生病  好吗  宝贝
You cannot get sick, okay, babe?
好  谢谢  宝贝
Okay. Thanks, baby.
伙计  你真没事吗
Hey, man, are you sure you're good?
哥们  我没事
Oh, dude, I'm fine.
-好  -别担心
- Okay. Nice. - Don't worry.
说真的  被尼克·弗瑞的麻醉剂刺中脖子
Seriously, getting tranq'd in the neck by Nick Fury,
可能是我遇到的最酷的事了
probably the coolest thing ever happen to me anyway.
-是挺酷的  -是啊
- It is pretty awesome. - Yeah.
我只是庆幸我不用去布拉格
I'm just happy I don't have to go to Prague.
-是啊  -好消息
- Seriously. - Good news.
我们要去布拉格了
We're going to Prague.
-什么  -布拉格
- What? - Prague?
是啊  旅游公司来电  他们给我们升了级
Yeah. Tour company called. They upgraded us.
你们真该听到我怎么在电话上教训他们的
You should've heard me on the phone with them.
我让他们知道厉害了
I really gave them hell.
我只听到你哭了
All I heard was crying.
看我们的升级版交通工具
Look at our upgraded ride.
哥们  看啊
Bro, you see that?
太赞了
It's pretty sick.
厉害啊  哈林顿老师
I'm impressed, Mr. Harrington.
不是吧
Oh, come on.
彼得  怎么...这怎么回事
Peter, what...? What's going on?
我觉得尼克·弗瑞挟持了我们的暑假假期
I think Nick Fury just hijacked our summer vacation.
中城高中
我是哈林顿老师  孩子们的...
I'm, uh, Mr. Harrington to the kids...
-好吧  -好
- Oh, all right. - Okay.
太赞了
Awesome.
是啊  赞
Yeah. Awesome.
奥地利  东阿尔卑斯山
好啊  弗拉粉  是F哥
Yo, what's up, Flash Mob? It's your boy, the Big F,
我的私人司机德米崔在带我游览阿尔卑斯山
cruising through the Alps with my private driver, Dimitri.
布拉格最浪漫的十个地方
查尔斯桥
"给下一个托尼·斯塔克  我信任你
"For the next Tony Stark, I trust you.
说伊迪丝"
Say EDITH."
准备进行虹膜和生物识别扫描
Stand by for retinal and biometric scan.
虹膜和生物识别扫描吻合
Retinal and biometric scan accepted.
彼得·帕克
-你好  -你好  彼得
- Hello? - Hello, Peter.
我是伊迪丝
I am EDITH,
托尼·斯塔克增强现实安全和防御系统
Tony Stark's augmented-reality security and defense system.
-他为我造了你吗  -不是
- So he made you for me? - No.
-但你能使用托尼所有的协议  -酷
- But you have access to all of Tony's protocols. - Cool.
你想看看我的功能吗
Would you like to see what I can do?
伊迪丝是"死后我仍是英雄"的缩写
EDITH stands for "Even dead, I'm the hero."
托尼就喜欢缩写
Tony loved his acronyms.
是啊
Yeah, he did.
我能调用整个斯塔克全球安全网络
I have access to the entire Stark Global Security network,
包括多个国防卫星
including multiple defense satellites,
以及各大电讯网络的后门
as well as back doors to all major telecommunication networks.
MJ在发短信吗
Is MJ texting?
不  别看
No. Don't look at it. Don't look at it.
那是不对的
That's wrong. That's wrong.
想你了
我更想你
加油  上厕所  10分钟
Petrol and toilets. Ten minutes!
弗拉粉  我们就在做这个...
Flash Mob, this is what we doing out here...
厕所  厕所在哪边
Toilet, toilet, toilet. Which way to the toilet?
10分钟  各位
Ten minutes, everyone.
德米崔  我们究竟在哪
Dimitri, where exactly are we?
-好吧  -天啊
- Okay. - Oh, my gosh,
-我自己搞明白吧  -这里太赞了
- I'll figure it out. - it's so sick.
真美啊
It's beautiful.
干什么
What?
你好
Hello.
关门
Close the door.
我是彼得·帕克
I'm Peter Parker.
脱衣服
Take off your clothes.
-什么  -你跟弗瑞说
- Excuse me? - You told Fury
蜘蛛侠不能出现在欧洲
Spider-Man cannot be seen in Europe.
所以我给你另做了套战衣
So I made you this, another suit.
谢谢
Thank you.
肯定合身的  我不用试...
I'm sure it fits fine. I don't need to try...
-脱衣服  -好
- Take off your clothes. - Okay.
行
Sure.
-有点尴尬  -快点的
- It's a little embarrassing. - Now. Hurry up.
好奇怪
This is weird.
不不  别
No, no, no. Don't...
抱歉  我以为这是厕所
Sorry. I thought this was the bathroom.
不是看上去那样的
This is not what it looks like.
-别  -好吧
- Just... - Yeah.
你干什么
What are you doing?
-布拉德  -不打扰你们了
- Brad. - I'll leave you two alone.
天啊
Oh, my God.
别开枪  布拉德
Don't shoot anybody. Brad?
不是看上去那样的  伙计
It's not what it looks like, buddy.
-哥们  听着  -彼得
- Hey, man, look, that's... - Look, Peter,
我不会评判你的人生选择  哥们
I'm not here to judge your life choices, dude.
如果你想在学校出游时  找个陌生欧洲妹
If you want to hook up with some random European chick,
-来一发  那是你的事  -不
- on our school trip, that's on you. - No.
不是那样的  真的
That's not what that was, honestly.
我不能假装我没看到那一幕
I can't pretend I didn't see what I saw.
我知道你想泡MJ  太明显了
I know you're trying to get with MJ. It's obvious.
-但我也喜欢她  -等等的
- But I like her too. - Wait a minute.
你不能给她看那张照片  哥们  拜托
You cannot show her that photo, dude. Come on.
抱歉  我必须给她看
I'm sorry, man. I have to.
她应该知道真相
She deserves the truth.
好了  一次一只脚
Okay, put your one foot in front of the other,
都给我上车
and, everybody, back on the bus.
10分钟了  快走
It's been 10 minutes. Let's go!
-伊迪丝  -你好  彼得
- EDITH? - Hello, Peter.
有什么需要帮助的
How can I help you?
我班上有个人要毁了一切了...
There's this guy in my class who's gonna ruin everything...
彼得  我听不清你说话
Peter, I'm having difficulty hearing you.
可以大声点吗
Can you please speak up?
布拉德·戴维斯  他拍了张我的照片
Brad Davis. He has a photo of me.
布拉德·戴维斯  他是目标吗
Brad Davis. Is he a target?
布拉德是目标吗
Is Brad a target?
对  他是目标
Yeah. He's a target. He's a target.
收到
Copy that.
目标是布拉德·戴维斯
Target is Brad Davis.
启动攻击
Initiating strike.
启动什么
Initiating what, now?
拦截点已确定
Intercept point determined.
-出动击杀战机  -伊迪丝
- Releasing kill vehicle. - EDITH.
-天啊  -眼镜真酷  帕克
- Oh, my God. - Dope glasses, Parker.
-你怎么买得起  -弗拉士  还我
- How'd you pay for these? - Flash, give them back.
-不不不  -还我  弗拉士
- No, no, no. - Give it to me, Flash.
-我在真心称赞你  -还我...
- I'm really paying you a compliment. - Please give me...
真对不起
I'm so sorry.
伊迪丝  别杀布拉德
EDITH, don't kill Brad.
彼得  你是否要我取消
Peter, do you want me to cancel
针对布拉德·戴维斯的无人机打击
the drone strike on Brad Davis?
-你刚打了弗拉士吗  -没有[不是]
- Did you just punch Flash? - No.
开火
Firing.
小心
Oh, look out!
这可不是高速路
This is not the autobahn!
-伊迪丝  -哈林顿
- EDITH. - Harrington!
开始第二次打击
Commencing second strike.
彼得  马上给我坐在座位上  系好安全带
Peter. Plant your fanny and buckle up, right now.
看那些小山羊
Look at the baby mountain goats!
-小山羊  -我看到了
- Baby mountain goats? - Ooh, I see them.
我没看到小山羊
I don't see any mountain goats.
你错过了
You missed them.
我知道你以为我们都没发现  彼得
I know you think none of us have noticed, Peter...
什么
What?
但你的新造型  我喜欢
...but your new look, I love it.
-是吧  宝贝  -谢谢
- Right, babe? - Thanks.
是啊  成熟  有格调  很欧洲
Yeah. Sophisticated, classy, very European.
天啊
Oh, man.
我们再来一次
Let's try that again.
好奇怪  本来就在我手机里的
This is so weird. It was right here on my phone.
-我...  -是啊  奇怪
- I-I... - Yeah. Weird.
捷克共和国  布拉格
-太美了  -这可真棒
- Freaking beautiful. - This is amazing.
这地方好高档
This place is so classy.
是啊  我们为什么会来这里
Yeah, so why are we here?
那是你的感觉
Speak for yourself.
我可是到家了
I'm home.
我还能说什么
What can I say?
会叫的轮子有升级油抹
The squeaky wheel gets the upgrade grease.
大家安顿下来  休息好  今晚  大惊喜哦
Everyone get settled in, rest up because tonight, big surprise,
是布拉格的年度
is Prague's annual...
-灯光嘉年华  -好啊
- ...Carnival of Lights. - Yeah!
-喂  -帕克  我是希尔
- Hello? - Parker, it's Hill.
你的战衣上有耳机
There's an earpiece with your suit.
戴上  等待进一步指示
Put it on and await further instructions.
-明白了吗  -是  女士
- Understood? - Uh, yes, ma'am.
-好  -伙计
- Yeah. - Hey, man.
如果我让你觉得
Look, I am so sorry
我只顾着自己恋爱  那很抱歉
if I seem like I'm preoccupied with my relationship.
我还是你的技术支援
You know, I'm still your guy in the chair.
不  没事  别担心
No, it's all good. Don't worry about it.
-那太好了  -没事
- Okay. Great, great. - It's fine.
那些元素怪什么情况了
So, what's the status on the Elemental thing?
-会在哪里出现  -在这座城市里
- Where's it gonna happen? - Uh, here in the city.
-彼得  我们在这儿呢  -我知道  不妙
- Peter, we're here. - I know, I know. It's not good.
我在想办法呢
It's... I'm figuring it out.
你得做点什么  彼得  拜托
You have to do something, Peter, please.
我们都指望你了
We're all counting on you.
-内德  -来了  宝贝
- Ned. - Yeah. Yeah, babe.
好消息是  我们都有单间
The good news is, we've all got our own rooms.
-可算  -不是吧
- It's about time. - Serious?
-帕克  -是  先生
- Parker? Parker! - Yes, sir.
那玩意几小时后就来了
That thing is going to be here in a few hours.
-我们让你无聊了吗  -他不是无聊
- Are we boring you? - He's not bored.
他只是在想被你绑架来的事
He's just thinking about how you kidnapped him.
他有困难
He had obstacles.
我解决掉了困难
I removed them.
他们还是不肯疏散城市
And they still won't evacuate the city.
白痴
Idiots.
怎么办  帕克
So, what's the plan, Parker?
我去大教堂塔楼
I will be in the cathedral tower,
留意火怪的出现
keeping watch for the fire monster.
等它出现  我就呼叫你们
When that shows up, I will radio you guys,
-然后我和贝克先生  -我叫神秘客
- and then Mr. Beck and I will... - My name is Mysterio.
然后我和神秘客就冲上去
That's when Mysterio and I will move in.
彼得  听我说
Peter, listen to me.
最好的结果  唯一的好结果
The best hope you have, the only hope,
就是现在阻止它
is to stop it here now,
不惜一切
no matter what the cost.
尽量带他远离市民
Maneuver it away from civilians if you can,
但最重要的是让它远离金属
but most important, keep it away from metal.
如果它长得太大
If it gets too big,
就能开始汲取地球内核的力量
it'll be able to draw power from the Earth's core.
那样的话  它就不可阻挡了
After that, there's no way to stop it.
我的朋友都在这里呢
Hey, man, my friends are here.
我忍不住觉得我们给他们带来了危险
I can't help but think that we're putting them in danger.
你还担心我们伤害你的朋友
You're worried about us hurting your friends?
你  调动无人机袭击你自己的学校旅游大巴
You, who called a drone strike on your own school tour bus?
斯塔克给了你一套价值百万的
Stark gave you a multibillion-dollar
现实增强战术情报系统
A.R. Tactical intelligence system,
你首先就拿它
and the first thing you do with it
去炸你朋友
is try and blow up your friends.
在我看来  你显然没做好准备
It's clear to me that you were not ready for this.
弗瑞叫我来看看你
Fury asked me to come up here and see how you were doing.
他对冲你发脾气感到过意不去
He just... He felt bad about snapping at you.
是吗
Really?
这个地球上有反讽这回事吧
You guys do have sarcasm on this Earth, right?
你感觉怎么样
How you feeling?
我没想到我这个暑假还得拯救世界
I didn't think I was gonna have to save the world this summer.
我知道这话听上去很混蛋  但...
I know that makes me sound like such a jerk. I just...
我本来计划好了跟我喜欢的女孩...
I had this plan with this girl that I really like...
现在都毁了
and now it's all ruined.
想要正常生活不叫混蛋  孩子
You're not a jerk for wanting a normal life, kid.
这条路很艰辛
It's a hard path.
你会看到一些事  会做一些事
You see things. You do things.
你要做出选择
You make choices.
人们敬仰你
People look up to you...
即便你赢得战役  有时也会死人
and even if you win a battle, sometimes they die.
我喜欢你  彼得  你是个好孩子
I like you, Peter. You're a good kid.
我心里有些想对你说
There's a part of me that wants me to tell you, just...
转身离开这一切
turn around, run away from all this.
但我心里又清楚
Then there's another part of me
我们要对付的东西是什么样
that knows what we're about to fight,
这关乎到什么  我很高兴有你在
what's at stake, and I'm glad you're here.
我也是
Me too.
但你担心你的朋友
But you're worried about your friends.
对
Yeah.
我觉得我总害他们有危险
Just always feel like I'm putting them in danger.
让他们待在室内
Look, just get them inside
让他们在安全处待几小时
and keep them in a safe place for just a few hours.
他们会没事的
They'll be all right.
能有个人一起聊聊
It's really nice to have somebody to talk to about
超级英雄的事真好
superhero stuff, you know?
不客气
Anytime.
如果我们活下来了
And, hey, we survive this,
你还有一整个暑假能杀布拉德呢
you'll have all summer to kill Brad.
待会儿见
See you out there.
好
All right.
对不起
Scusi.
抱歉  那是意大利语
Sorry, that's Italian.
好了  伊迪丝  快点
Okay. EDITH? Oh, come on.
你好  彼得
Hello, Peter.
我需要想个办法让我的朋友们
I need to find a way to keep my friends
接下来几小时待在室内
inside the next few hours.
我们想想办法吧
Let's see what we can do.
好消息
Good news.
我们要去看歌剧
We're going to the opera!
-开什么玩笑  -歌剧
- You're kidding me. - The opera?
别看我
Don't look at me.
不是说去嘉年华吗
What happened to the carnival?
这就是升级人生
This is upgrade living, guys.
来嘛  门票是旅游公司免费送的
Come on. The tour company just gave us these tickets.
免费哦
For free!
你们知道歌剧门票多贵吗
Do you have any idea how much opera tickets cost?
不知道
No,
因为我们没有人想去看歌剧  从来不想
because none of us have ever wanted to go to the opera, ever.
我觉得这是我们增长文化知识的好机会
Well, I think this is gonna be culturally enriching for us.
谢谢  内德
Thank you, Ned.
各位  这或许将是
Everyone, this is gonna be, maybe,
我们整个旅程中最棒的四小时
the best four hours of our whole trip.
四小时
Four hours?
各位  我觉得这会很好玩的  真的
Guys, I think this is gonna be fun. Seriously.
你们肯定都庆幸我让你们带身好衣服了吧
I bet now you're all happy that I had you pack a nice outfit.
是啊  因为我们更想去看四小时的歌剧
Yeah, because we'd much rather go to a four-hour opera
而不是全世界最大的派对
instead of the biggest party in the world.
再说一次  跟我无关
Again, don't look at me.
帕克  收到吗
Parker, do you copy?
通讯检查  一  二
Comm check, one, two.
好  我们到了
Okay, here we are.
在人流之前到了
Beat the rush.
是啊  是往外走的人流
Yeah, the rush out.
我们走运  有最好的座位
Lucky for us, we got the best seats in the house.
走吧
Let's go.
我给你留个位置
I'll save you a seat.
你真美
You look really pretty.
因此我才有价值吗
And therefore, I have value?
不  我完全不是那意思
No. No, that's not what I meant at all. I was just...
我在逗你呢
I'm messing with you.
-谢谢  -不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
-你也很帅气  -谢谢
- You look pretty too. - Thank you.
-天啊  歌剧眼镜  -好可爱
- Oh, my gosh! Opera glasses! - So cute.
-我能...  -好
- Can I...? - Yeah.
想要一副吗[想一起坐吗]
Want to go in on a pair?
坐在一起吗
You mean, sit next to each other?
好啊
Yeah.
你就位了吗
Are you in position?
-没有[不想]  -好吧  算了
- No. - Okay. No...
为什么没有  帕克
Why the hell not? Parker?
你不想跟我坐一起吗
You don't want to sit next to me,
还是不想要眼镜
or, no, you just don't want the glasses?
我不是那意思
I didn't mean that.
你先去吧  我去给我们买一副
If you go ahead, I'll go grab us a pair.
我在我旁边给你留个座位
I'll save you a seat next to me.
-好  -座位很多
- Awesome. - A lot of seats,
我就在那边
so I'll be up there.
好
Okay.
-帕克  -我就来
- Parker. - No, I'm coming. I'm...
我得走了
I gotta go.
你能跟MJ说我病了什么的吗
Could you just tell MJ that I'm sick or something?
好吧  小心点
Okay. Be careful.
彼得  无论如何
And Peter, whatever you do,
千万让怪物离歌剧院远点
please steer the monster away from the opera house.
内德  我知道
Yeah, Ned, I know.
-好  -好吧
- Okay. - Okay?
-嗯  -我走了
- Yeah. - Gotta go.
帕克  你最好要来了
Parker! You better be on your way.
来了
Coming.
你觉得她是去哪
Where do you think she's going?
会是去嘉年华吗
Do you think she's going to the carnival?
-我不...  -我们也该去
- Oh, I... I don't... - We should go, too.
对  我们去吧
Yes, we should go.
我们走吧  走
Come on, let's go.
走
Come on.
好  我就位了
All right. I'm in position.
我一看到什么  贝克
As soon as I see something, Beck, I'll, uh...
我就告诉你
I'll let you know.
-收到  -战衣如何
- Roger that. - How's the suit?
很好  很棒
The suit's great. It's awesome.
射网处有点紧
It's a little tight around the old web-shooter.
帕克
Parker!
我闭嘴了
Okay, I'll shut up.
天啊  宝贝  这多美啊
Oh, my God, babe, isn't this beautiful?
是啊  真美啊  宝贝
Yeah, it's real beautiful, babe.
-怎么了  -老实说
- What's wrong? - You know, honestly, I just...
我不是很适应人多  要不我们...
I don't do well with big crowds, so maybe we should...
我知道怎么办
I have the perfect thing.
走
Come on.
别担心  宝贝
Don't worry, babe.
我们能远离人群  呼吸点新鲜空气
We'll get away from the crowds, get some fresh air.
你会感觉好得多的
You'll feel a thousand times better.
能量激增
Energy spiking.
还有地震活动
We have seismic activity.
他出现了
Okay, he's here!
贝克  准备好了吗
Beck, are you ready?
你知道怎么办
You know what to do.
听你的  蜘蛛侠
On your lead, Spider-Man.
不  回来
No, come back!
回来救我们
Come back and help us!
你上吧  孩子
You're up, kid.
等等  那是...
Wait, wait. Is that...?
你觉得那是蜘蛛侠吗
Do you think that's Spider-Man?
不不不
No, no, no.
那是他的欧洲山寨货
It's a European rip-off version of him.
我前两天还看他的报道了  不是他
I was actually read about him the other day. It's not him.
不  贝克  他吸收了旋转木马
No, Beck! He's got the carousel!
他在变大了
He's getting bigger!
他叫什么
What's his name? What's his name?
是夜猴侠
It's Night... Night Monkey.
-夜猴侠  -对  对
- Night Monkey? - Yeah. Yeah.
夜猴侠
Night Monkey!
-对  -夜猴侠  救命
- Yeah. - Night Monkey, help!
夜猴侠
Night Monkey.
-救我们  -什么
- Save us! - What?
夜猴侠  我们困住了
Night Monkey, we're stuck!
-不不  -救命
- Oh, no, no. - Help us! Help!
你没事吧
Are you okay?
-执行B计划吧  -好
- On to Plan B? - Yeah!
我们得拿它无法吸收的东西打它
We gotta hit him with something he can't absorb!
我左  你右
I go left, you go right!
动手
Now!
好  打它
Okay, shoot him!
好
Yeah!
伤到它了  继续
That hurt him. Keep it coming.
蜘蛛侠  保持距离
Spider-Man, keep your distance.
我在尽力
I'm trying!
别让它靠近摩天轮
Can't let him get near the Ferris wheel.
好  看我的
Okay. I'm on it!
那是什么
What is that?!
贝蒂  贝蒂
Betty! Betty!
就这样  好样的  你打中它了
That's it! Nice! Nice! You got him!
不不不
No, no, no.
太迟了
It's too late.
不管发生什么
Whatever happens...
很高兴我们相识一场
I'm glad we met.
贝克  你要干什么
Beck, what are you doing?
我上次该干的事
What I should have done last time.
贝克  别
Beck, don't do it!
贝克
Beck!
贝克先生
Mr. Beck?
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
我真想亲你
I would totally kiss you,
但我觉得我刚有点吐在嘴里了
but I think I just threw up in my mouth a little.
我可能有薄荷糖
I might have a mint.
结束了吗
So it's over?
那是最后一个了
That was the last of them.
但不会是我们最后一次面临威胁
But not the last threat we'll ever face.
我们得保持警惕
We need to stay vigilant.
这世界正缺你这样的人
There's a void in this world for someone like you.
希尔和我明天要去柏林的欧警总部
Hill and I are going to Europol headquarters in Berlin tomorrow.
你该一起来
You should join us.
谢谢  我可能真会去
Thank you. I just might take you up on that.
你有天赋  帕克
You got gifts, Parker,
但你不想来
but you didn't wanna be here.
弗瑞先生
Mr. Fury, I...
我希望你也能去柏林
I'd love to have you in Berlin too.
但你得想好  你要不要挺身而出
But you got to decide whether you're going to step up or not.
斯塔克选了你
Stark chose you.
他让你做了复仇者
He made you an Avenger.
我需要那个
I need that.
世界也需要
The world needs that.
或许斯塔克错了
Maybe Stark was wrong.
是吗
Was he?
选择权在你
The choice is yours.
我们去喝一杯吧
Let's get a drink.
我没到21
I'm not 21.
你该庆祝  我们今晚做了好事
You gotta celebrate. We did something good tonight.
是啊
Yeah.
弗瑞是对的
Fury was right.
托尼为我做了好多事
Tony did a lot for me, so...
我欠他的  欠大家的
I owe it to him, to everybody.
是吗
Do you?
对
Yeah. I mean...
斯塔克先生给了我做更多的机会
Mr. Stark gave me the chance to be more.
他希望我做的比他好
He wanted me to be better than him.
弗瑞希望我不负他的期望
And Fury just wants me to live up to that.
那你想要什么  彼得
What do you want, Peter?
-什么意思  -你想要什么
- What do you mean? - What do you want?
我不知道
I don't know.
你想要什么  彼得·帕克  就现在
What do you want? You, Peter Parker. Now.
我知道你在想
I know you're thinking about it.
我想去旅我的行
I wanna go on my trip, right?
我想回去跟朋友们一起旅行
I want to go back on my trip with my friends.
跟我喜欢的姑娘
And go to the top of the Eiffel Tower
去埃菲尔铁塔顶层  然后向她告白
with the girl who I really like and tell her how I feel, and...
吻她
give her a kiss.
闭嘴啦
Shut up, man.
你不会那么做  是吧
You're not gonna do that, are you?
-我不能  -为什么不能
- No, I can't. - Why not?
因为我还有太多责任
Because I have too much of a responsibility.
-天啊  非常感谢  -那是什么
- Oh, my God. Thank you so much. - What are those?
-那是...  -伊迪丝眼镜  是啊
- Are those the...? - EDITH glasses, yeah.
之前掉地上了吗
They were just on the floor?
戴上试试  让我看看
Try them on. Let's see how they look like.
-是吗  -嗯
- Yeah? - Yeah.
我还挺喜欢的
I actually really like them.
我能跟你说实话吗
Can I be completely honest with you?
请吧
Please.
丑爆了
They look really stupid.
但或许还有隐形眼镜版本的
But maybe they have a contact-lens version.
你戴上试试
You try them on.
-不  得了  -试试嘛
- No, come on. - Try them on.
-我不想戴  -戴上试试嘛
- I don't wanna try them on. - Just put them on.
你觉得怎么样  孩子
What do you think, kid?
"下一个托尼·斯塔克  我信任你"
"Next Tony Stark, I trust you."
"给下一个托尼·斯塔克  我信任你"
"For the next Tony Stark, I trust you."
什么
What?
斯塔克先生给我留下眼镜时还有段话
Mr Stark left me a message with those glasses:
"给下一个托尼·斯塔克  我信任你"
"For the next Tony Stark, I trust you."
我还是不懂  你喝了几杯柠檬汁
I'm still not following. How many lemonades have you had?
他知道我犯过的每个错误
He knew every mistake I ever made.
他肯定也知道我还没做好这个准备
So, he must've known that I wasn't ready for something like this.
那他为什么要把眼镜给你
Why would he give it to you?
因为或许他不是把伊迪丝托付给了我
Because maybe he didn't trust me to have EDITH,
而是托付我选个应该拥有它的人
he just trusted me to pick who should.
这要合理多了  他一向知道我会做正确选择
It makes much more sense. He always knew I'd do what's right.
他不会把眼镜给弗瑞的
And he's not gonna give them to Fury
因为弗瑞只会自己留着伊迪丝
because Fury would give himself EDITH.
这你八成是说对了
You're probably right about that.
是啊  所以世界需要下一个钢铁侠
Right, so the world needs the next Iron Man.
那不会是我的  我是个皇后区来的16岁孩子
And it's not me. I mean, I'm a 16-year-old kid from Queens.
得是个大人  有经验
It needs to be an adult with some experience
就像托尼·斯塔克一样好  比如你
and that's good like Tony Stark, like you.
不  彼得  得了
No. Peter, come on.
不行
No.
-伊迪丝  -你好  彼得
- EDITH? - Hello, Peter.
嗯
Yeah, um...
我想把你的控制权交给昆廷·贝克
I'd like to transfer your control over to Quentin Beck.
-彼得  你干什么呢  -做正确的事
- Peter, what are you doing? - Doing the right thing.
移交控制权需要确认
Any transfer will require confirmation.
斯塔克把眼镜给了你
Stark gave you the glasses.
斯塔克给了我个选择
Stark gave me a choice.
这是我要做的选择  我现在要选了
It's my choice to make. Okay? I'm gonna make it.
你是个士兵  是领袖  你阻止了元素怪
Look, you're a soldier, a leader. You stopped the Elementals.
你救了我  救了世界  好吗
You saved my life. You saved the world, okay?
他会希望你拿着眼镜的
He'd want you to have them.
等待确认
Waiting for confirmation.
确认
Confirm.
欢迎加入复仇者联盟
Welcome to the Avengers.
你戴挺帅的
They look good on you.
谢谢
Thank you.
很荣幸
It's an honor.
嗯
Yeah.
斯塔克先生真的会喜欢你的
Mr. Stark would've really liked you.
-你去哪  -去找MJ
- Where you headed? - I'm gonna go find MJ.
祝你好运  孩子  我觉得你有一半机会
Good luck, kid. I'll give you about a fifty-fifty chance.
你挺别扭的
You're pretty awkward. So...
嗯
Yeah.
-回见了  -回见
- See you later, man. - See you.
瞧  并不难吧
See? That wasn't so hard.
太好了
Yes!
谁帮我褪下这身破戏服
Somebody get this stupid costume off me!
好  我们拿到伊迪丝了
Okay, we got EDITH.
把这个连上我们的系统
Get these connected to our system.
敬酒
Toast! Toast! Toast!
这是场重大胜利  但我们的任务还很艰巨
Now, this is a big win, but we still got a lot of work to do.
敬酒
Toast! Toast! Toast!
好啊
Yeah!
好吧  敬一杯
Okay, toasts!
给我  道格
Give me that, Doug.
敬让我们走到一起的人
To the man who brought us all together,
我们的前老板  托尼·斯塔克
our former boss, Tony Stark.
小丑国王
The jester king.
被财富和科技包裹
Literally wrapped in wealth and technology
他却不配使用它们
that he was unfit to wield.
就像我设计的全息系统
Like the holographic system I designed.
那是革命性的突破
A revolutionary breakthrough
有无限的应用前景
with limitless applications
却被托尼变成了自我治疗机器  还改名叫...
that Tony turned into a self-therapy machine and renamed...
二进制增强记忆重塑工具  简称"二重"[吐]
Binarily Augmented Retro-Framing, or BARF.
我这个治疗实验花费了6.11亿美元
$611 million for my little therapeutic experiment.
他把我的毕生心血改名叫
He renamed my life's work...
"二重"
"Barf."
我对他说这是个错误
I told him it was a mistake,
我的科技可以改变世界
that my technology could change the world.
然后
And then...
他解雇了我
he fired me.
说我...
Said I was...
不稳定
unstable.
敬托尼
To Tony.
To Tony!
接下来  敬威廉
Next, to William.
威廉
William!
托尼·斯塔克在一个山洞里就造成了
Tony Stark was able to build this in a cave!
用的是一堆破烂
With a box of scraps!
我的幻景科技和你的
The integration of my illusion tech
武器化无人机的结合简直绝妙
with your weaponized drones was brilliant.
强大幻景  真实摧毁  屡试不爽
Powerful illusions, real damage, worked like a charm.
而这还只是开始
And it's just the beginning.
-谢谢  兄弟  -敬古特曼
- Thank you, brother. - To Guterman.
-古特曼  -敬古特曼
- Guterman! - To Guterman!
你编写的故事
The story you created
一个来自另一个地球的战士昆廷
of a soldier from another Earth named Quentin
在欧洲跟太空怪物战斗  简直荒谬至极
fighting space monsters in Europe is totally ridiculous
可看来现在
and apparently exactly the kind of thing
大家就信这一套了
people would believe right now.
所有人都信了
I mean, everybody bought it.
-古特  -古特曼
- Gutes! - Guterman!
-敬维多利亚  -敬维多利亚
- To Victoria. - To Victoria!
在每个袭击点制造电磁脉冲
Staging electromagnetic pulses at each attack site
让弗瑞的卫星确认我们的谎言
so Fury's own satellites would confirm our lies.
好点子
Inspired idea.
-敬詹妮丝  -詹妮丝
- To Janice. - Janice!
托尼死后  是她发现了
After Tony died, she was the one who discovered that
伊迪丝没有被交给我们
EDITH was being handed over not to us,
或是国防部
not to the Defense Department,
而是给了个孩子
but to a child.
-谢谢  -敬詹妮丝
- Thank you. - To Janice!
也敬你们其他人  托尼·斯塔克死了
And to the rest of you, Tony Stark is gone.
现在有个机会  会有人站出来的
There's a window of opportunity, and someone will step up.
但现如今  哪怕你是在场最聪明的人
But these days, you can be the smartest guy in the room,
最有资质的人  也没人在乎
the most qualified, and no one cares.
除非你披着斗篷飞
Unless you're flying around with a cape
或是手能发出激光
or shooting lasers from your hands,
否则根本没人听你说话
no one will even listen.
我现在有斗篷和激光了
Well, I've got a cape and lasers.
凭借我们的科技  和伊迪丝
With our technology and with EDITH,
神秘客将成为地球上最伟大的英雄
Mysterio will be the greatest hero on Earth!
好啊
Yeah!
到时所有人都得听着
Then everyone will listen!
不是听一个酗酒的巨婴
Not to a boozy man-child.
不
No!
也不是听一个青春期少年
Not to a hormonal teenager.
不
No!
而是听我
To me...
以及我很富有的手下
and to my very wealthy crew.
敬我们
To us.
敬神秘客
To Mysterio!
敬彼得·帕克
To Peter Parker.
To Peter Parker!
可怜的孩子
Poor kid.
我们开工吧
Let's get to work.
彼得  天啊
Peter, oh, my God.
我们差点死了
We almost died.
没事的
It's fine. It's fine.
我的任务执行完了
Guess what, I'm done with the mission.
-哥们  旅行结束了  -什么
- Dude, the trip's over. - What?
我们去哪都有怪物从地下钻出来
There's monsters coming out of the ground everywhere we go.
我们的家长当然会叫我们回去了
Of course our parents would want us home.
请别让我待机  彼得  你没死
Don't put me on hold. Peter, you're not dead.
天啊  太好了  待在这里
Oh, my God. Yes, good. Stay here.
别...去换身衣服  我们在订飞机
Don't... Put some clothes on. We're booking flights.
我们为科学而来  却因巫术而走
We came for science, we're leaving because of witches.
欢迎来到新黑暗时代
Welcome to the new Dark Ages.
-怎么回事  -我们一早就回家
- What is going on, dude? - We're going home in the morning.
不不  元素怪都没了
No, no, no. All the Elementals are gone.
-内德  -来了  亲爱的
- Ned. - Coming, sweetie.
你们能小点声吗  我在直播
Can you guys keep it down? I'm live-streaming.
好
Yeah.
你去哪了
Where were you?
我迷路了
I got lost.
我们担心你来着
We were worried about you.
幸好你回来了
Good thing you're back.
是啊
Yeah.
巴黎去不成了  是吧
So much for Paris, right?
本会很好玩的
It would've been fun.
是啊
Yeah.
晚安
Night.
你真美...
You look ni...
好吧
Okay.
那个
Look, um...
我还不希望旅行就此结束
I'm not ready for this trip to be over yet, and
我想做点有趣的事
I kind of want to do something fun
不在日程上  不是规划好的事
that's not on the itinerary or planned
也没有哈林顿老师陪着
or with Mr. Harrington.
好
Yes.
"好"  你想去吗
"Yes," Like you wanna go?
对
Yes.
太好了  那10分钟后外面见
Okay. Awesome. I'll see you outside in 10 minutes.
五分钟后外面见
Meet me outside in five minutes.
-五分钟也行  -好
- Five is good. - Okay.
-好  再见  -再见
- Okay, bye. - Bye.
夜猴侠  救命  夜猴侠
Night Monkey, help us! Help! Night Monkey!
你想去哪
So where do you wanna go?
-管他呢  -好啊
- Who cares? - Awesome.
-好  -走吧
- Okay. - Let's go.
我很高兴我们能出来走走
I'm glad we're doing this.
-是啊  我也是  -看看这座城市
- Yeah, me too. - To see the city a bit.
人们以前会在这座桥上执行处决
You know, they used to execute people on this bridge.
把人放进篮子里
They would put them in a basket,
丢进水里淹死
and they would drown in the water.
-抱歉  -没事
- Sorry. - It's okay.
有件事
There's this thing that
我想跟你说  想了好一阵了
I've been wanting to talk to you about for a while.
什么事
Yeah?
这是我们在欧洲的最后一晚了
It's our last night in Europe,
我有个计划  我想告诉你
and I had this plan that I wanted to tell you.
我就说了
I'm just gonna tell you.
MJ  我
MJ, I...
"我是蜘蛛侠"
"I'm Spider-Man."
-什么  -那是你想说的吧
- What? - That's what you were gonna say.
你是蜘蛛侠
That you're Spider-Man.
不  我不是蜘蛛侠
No. I'm not Spider-Man.
我观察你好一阵了
I mean, I've been watching you for a while now.
挺明显的
It's kind of obvious.
我不是蜘蛛侠
I'm not Spider-Man.
你为什么会觉得我是蜘蛛侠
What would make you think that I was Spider-Man?
-彼得  华盛顿  -什么
- Peter, Washington? - Yeah?
你突然之间毫无道理地不见了
The fact that you disappear out of nowhere for no reason.
不  我病了  记得吗
No, I was sick. Remember?
我...肚子疼
I had my... The tummy?
苏珊·杨以为你是个男妓
You know, Susan Yang thinks you're a male escort.
什么  我当然不是男妓
What? No. Of course I'm not a male escort.
那你就是蜘蛛侠
Well, then you're Spider-Man.
-不  我才不是蜘蛛侠  -那今晚呢
- No, I'm not Spider-Man at all. - What about tonight?
你溜出去  跟那怪物打斗  我看到了
You snuck off and you fought that thing. I saw you.
你不可能看到我  因为我不是蜘蛛侠
You can't have seen me because I'm not Spider-Man.
而且新闻上说那是夜猴侠
And also, on the news, it was the Night Monkey.
-夜猴侠  -对
- The Night Monkey? - Yeah.
新闻上那么说的
That's what it said on the news,
新闻从不撒谎
and the news never lies.
夜猴侠  好吧
Night Monkey. Okay.
你干什么
What are you doing?
夜猴侠和蜘蛛侠
Well, do the Night Monkey and Spider-Man
用一样的网吗
use the same webs?
或许吧
I mean, maybe.
或许他是只蜘蛛猿  谁知道呢
Maybe he's a Spider Monkey. Who knows?
你看我
Were you only watching me
只是因为你以为我是蜘蛛侠吗
because you thought I was Spider-Man?
对啊
Yeah.
要不然我为什么要看你
Why else would I be watching you?
无所谓了
Doesn't matter.
就是以为...
Just thought that maybe...
那怎么回事
What the hell was that?
我不知道
I don't know.
那是什么投影仪吗
What is it, like some kind of projector or something?
对  但非常先进
Yeah, but it's really advanced.
看上去好真
It... It looked so real.
是啊  非常真
Yeah, really real.
-等等  那么说...  -元素怪是假的
- Wait, does that mean that...? - The Elementals are fake?
但那没道理  因为我们在场的
That doesn't make any sense because we were there, right?
现场有火  还造成了毁灭
There was fire and destruction, and...
谁会做出那种事啊
Who would do something like that?
神秘客
Mysterio.
我是蜘蛛侠
I am Spider-Man.
我坏大事了
And I've really messed up.
等等  你现在说真的吗
Wait. You're b-being serious right now?
你没开玩笑  你百分百认真的吗
You're not joking with me? Like, you're 100 percent serious?
-因为这不好笑  -我没开玩笑
- Because it's not funny. - No, I'm not joking.
因为我本来只有67%确定
Because I was only like 67 percent sure.
-MJ  -那你为什么在这儿
- MJ... - So why are you here?
你为什么来参加学习出游
Why are you on this school trip?
我知道你有千万个问题
Look, I know you have a lot of questions,
但我们真得走了
but look, we really have to get out of here, okay?
好  真不敢相信我猜到了
Okay. Okay. I can't believe I figured it out!
你夺走了我的一切
You took everything from me!
这是为了我家人
This is for my family!
暂停
Pause.
抱歉
Sorry.
可以快进到最后吗
Yeah, can you just fast-forward to the end?
好  稍等
Yep. Stand by.
好  飞飞飞  射射射
All right, fly, fly, fly, zap, zap, zap.
暂停  我不太喜欢这走位
Pause. I'm not in love with this choreography,
但也凑合了
but it'll do.
关闭图像
Kill image.
无人机显形
De-cloak drones.
好  武器
All right, weapons.
-你要武器化吗  -对
- You want to weaponize? - Yep.
启用武器  准备
Weapons only. Stand by.
很好
Nice.
停下
Stop.
有点...我也说不清
Something. I don't know what it is.
但有点
It's something...
这样吧
Just dou... You know what?
破坏力翻倍  再来一遍
Double the damage and then run it again.
要我翻倍吗
You want me to double it up?
-对  -好
- Yeah. - All right.
堵耳朵
Cover your ears.
很好  就这样
That is good! That's good.
-时间没问题吧  -没问题
- We on schedule? - Oh, yeah.
向伊迪丝网络上传软件破解
Uploading software hack to EDITH network.
有了它的无人机
With her drones,
我们就能制造一起足以覆盖整个城市的事件
we'll be able to create an event big enough to cover an entire city.
好样的  确保每台无人机都能调用武器
All right. Well done. Make sure every drone is weapons-hot.
我们需要最大破坏
We need maximum damage.
-那会死伤惨重的  -当然
- That's gonna cause a lot of casualties. - Oh, yeah.
伤亡大  报道多  我得盖过其他新闻
More casualties, more coverage. I gotta cut through the static.
伦敦是座美丽的城市  它会遭殃
London's a beautiful city, and it'll suffer,
但他们能重建  如果我想做下个钢铁侠
but they can rebuild. I mean, if I'm gonna be the next Iron Man,
我得在复仇者级别的威胁下拯救世界
I need to save the world from an Avengers-level threat.
但等它的新救世主到来
But when its new savior descends,
那些伤亡都会被遗忘
all those casualties will be forgotten.
詹妮丝  你要就位  准备让我速换盔甲
Janice, you'll be in position with my quick-change armor
-去迎接胜利  -没问题
- for the victory lap? - Of course.
-你想试试...  -不
- You wanna try...? - No, that's...
我的手怎么了  怎么会这样
What's going on with my hand? Why is that happening?
从广场上回来的一台无人机
One of the drones that came back from the plaza
丢了个投影仪  没事的
was missing a projector. It's fine.
等等  你...你才告诉我吗
Wait, and you're...? You're telling me this now?
就一台无人机  图像不会有问题的  我保证
It's one drone. The image will be perfect, I promise.
那台投影仪是证据
That projector is evidence.
能让人们知道我们在做什么
It's gonna tell people what we're doing
怎么做到的
and how we're doing it.
我可是在努力骗过70亿人
I am trying to fool 7 billion people here,
包括尼克·弗瑞  他可是全世界最多疑
including Nick Fury, who happens to be the most paranoid
也最危险的人
and most dangerous person on the planet.
如果他在我杀了他前发现了
And if he catches on before I've killed him,
他会一枪崩了我的脑袋
and he will put a bullet in my head.
没人想被一枪崩了脑袋  是吧
And nobody wants a bullet in their head, right?
是吧
Right?
威廉  你看着我
William, can you look at me?
调出伊迪丝
Pull up EDITH.
你好  昆廷
Hello, Quentin.
亲爱的  启动五级搜索
Hi, honey. I need a level-five search,
全资源协议  查找这个装置
full-resource protocol for this device.
正在放大
Magnifying.
那里  搜索进出那栋建筑的一切
There. Search everything going in and out of that building.
已找到
Located.
该死
Shit.
威廉  有一天
You know, William, one day,
等我因为这个不得不杀了彼得·帕克
after I've had to kill Peter Parker because of this,
我希望你记得  他的血是沾在你手上的
I hope you remember that his blood is on your hands!
真不敢相信我把眼镜给了贝克
I can't believe I gave Beck those glasses.
我怎么能那么蠢
I mean, how could I be that stupid?
他大概此刻正在监视我
He's probably spying on me right now
或是派无人机来杀我
or sending a drone to come and kill me.
你还能调用杀人无人机吗
You had access to killer drones?
对  我并没想要的
Yeah, I didn't really want them,
尤其是在我差点杀了布拉德之后
especially after I almost killed Brad.
你差点杀了布拉德
You almost killed Brad?
听着  我得打给弗瑞先生
Look, I have to call Mr. Fury
告诉他贝克是骗子
and tell him that Beck's a fraud, but...
但他应该监听了我的电话
I think he tapped my phone.
好吧  那你怎么办
Okay. So, what are you gonna do?
我需要我的战衣
I need my suit,
我得去柏林  跟弗瑞先生当面说
and I have to go to Berlin and talk to Mr. Fury in person.
那个...
Just...
内德  太好了
Ned, perfect.
这戏服太棒了
The costume looks great...
穿去化装舞会太合适了
for the costume party
就在王子城堡
at the prince's castle.
她知道了  我告诉她了
She knows. I told her.
不是他告诉我的  是我猜到的
He didn't tell me. I figured it out.
太棒了
That's cool.
老早就猜到了
Like, a long time ago.
神秘客是个骗子
Look, Mysterio is a fraud.
但他救了我和贝蒂
But he saved me and Betty's lives.
不  他用幻景科技伪造了整件事
No. He's been faking the whole thing with illusion tech.
对  他使用了全息投影仪
Yeah, he's using these, like, hologram projectors.
真疯狂
That's crazy.
是啊
Yeah.
所以你们是要一起查案吗
So you guys were like working the case together or what?
主要是靠我
It's been mostly me.
内德  打给梅  让她打给哈林顿老师
Look, Ned, I need you to call May, get her to call Mr. Harrington,
说她希望我去柏林亲戚家住
say that she wanted me to stay with family in Berlin,
等待风波过去  好吗
until this all blows over. Okay?
好的  轻松
Got it. Easy.
你们撒谎真是驾轻就熟
You guys lie with such ease.
我得走了
I gotta go.
等等  投影仪
Wait, wait, wait. The projector.
你会需要这个的
You're gonna need this.
别跟任何人说
Don't tell anyone about this, okay?
知道的人都会有危险
Anyone who knows is in danger.
所以  你也知道了
So you know too.
真酷  虽然是我先知道的  而且要更早
It's cool. I mean, I've known first, and I've known longer,
但又不是什么竞争
but it's not a competition.
德国  柏林
不好意思  你知道哪...
Excuse me. Do you know where...?
-夜猴侠  -不  等等  我不...天啊
- Nacht Monkey! - No, wait, I didn't... Oh, man.
上车
Get in.
弗瑞先生
Mr. Fury...
你要解释很多事了
You've got a lot of explaining to do.
-不不  听着  -等安全了再说
- No, no, no, listen. - Wait until we're secure.
好
Okay.
对哦
Right.
你要跟我们说说
So is there anything you want to tell us
你的女朋友吗
about your girlfriend?
他是指伊迪丝
He's talking about EDITH.
我知道我犯了个错误  我很抱歉
Look, I know I made a mistake, I'm sorry,
但他不是你想的那样
but he is not who you think he is.
贝克是个骗子  神秘客  元素怪
Beck is a liar. Mysterio, the Elementals,
都是假的  他有种幻景科技
it's all fake. He has some illusion tech.
他就是这样骗了你  还骗我把伊迪丝交给了他
And that's how he tricked you guys, and me into giving him EDITH.
这是个投影仪
It's a projector.
我从布拉格的火怪身上拽下来的
I pulled it off the fire monster in Prague.
我们看到的一切死亡和毁灭
So all that death and destruction we witnessed
都是这个假造的
was created by this?
不  不光是这个  我觉得他在用无人机
No, not just this. I think he's using drones.
如果真是如此
Well, if this is true,
那贝克就非常危险  我们也得机智应对
then Beck's very dangerous and we need to be smart.
你还告诉谁了
Who else did you tell about this?
帕克  帕克
Parker? Parker!
-怎么了  -贝克  他在这儿
- What's wrong? - It's Beck. He's here.
什么  希尔
What? Hill?
不  只是幻...
No, it's just an illu...
弗瑞
Fury!
彼得
Peter.
我以为我们很要好呢
I thought we were close.
弗瑞本就必须死  但你不一样
Fury always had to die, but not you.
别躲了  贝克
Stop hiding, Beck!
我本想帮你离开这一切
I tried to help you walk away.
这下你逼我不得不动手了
Now you're making me do this.
是你说  你只是个孩子
You told me, you were just a kid.
是你说  你想去追那姑娘
You told me, you wanted to run after that girl.
-救命  -MJ
- Help me! - MJ!
天啊
Oh, God!
彼得  怎么回事
Peter, what's going on?
我知道这是假的
I know this isn't real.
你确定吗
Do you, though?
MJ
MJ!
我看你分不清真假了  彼得
I don't think you know what's real, Peter.
你需要醒过来
You need to wake up!
看看你自己
I mean, look at yourself.
你只是个害怕的孩子
You are just a scared little kid
穿着件运动衫
in a sweat suit.
我创造了神秘客
I created Mysterio
好给世界一个可以信仰的人
to give the world someone to believe in.
我控制真相
I control the truth.
神秘客就是真相
Mysterio is the truth.
如果你真够好
If you were good enough,
或许托尼就不会死了
maybe Tony would still be alive.
安托尼·爱德华·斯塔克
内心深处  你知道我是对的
Deep down, you know I'm right.
你自己做了选择
You made your choice.
你只需要让位
And all you had to do was step aside.
现在你...
And now you have...
弗瑞
Fury.
贝克的人想找到
Beck's people are trying to find
所有能曝光他们的人
everyone who could expose him.
你告诉谁了
Who'd you tell?
我知道你跟人说了
I know you told someone...
告诉我吧
...so just tell me.
-好  -你告诉谁了
- Okay. - Who did you tell?
你还告诉谁了
Who else did you tell?
就我班上的内德和MJ
Just Ned and MJ from my class.
内德可能告诉他女友贝蒂了
Maybe Ned told his girlfriend Betty,
但没别的了
but that's it.
怎么了
What?
你太好骗了
You are so gullible.
-什么  -虽然很聪明
- What? - I mean, you're smart as a whip.
但是...
Just a...
太好骗了
...sucker.
现在你的朋友也都得死了
And now all your friends have to die.
天啊
Oh, my God.
骗那些
It's easy to fool people
已经在自我欺骗的人很容易
when they're already fooling themselves.
但不管如何  彼得
But for what it's worth, Peter,
我真的很抱歉
I really am sorry.
-伊迪丝  -是  昆廷
- EDITH. - Yes, Quentin.
读取彼得·帕克班级旅行的资料
Access files to Peter Parker's class trip.
我要他们在伦敦转机回家
I need them to fly home from London.
我在哪
Where am I?
城市监禁中心
Municipal holding facility.
他们说他们在火车场发现了昏迷不醒的你
They said they found you unconscious at the train yard.
很危险啊
Very dangerous.
我们给了你件衬衫
And we gave you the shirt
因为你似乎有点冷
because you seemed a bit cold.
谢谢
Thanks.
你们真好
You guys are nice.
你们的英语说得真好
You speak really good English.
欢迎来到荷兰
Welcome to the Netherlands.
我在荷兰吗
I'm in the Netherlands right now?
对
Yep.
再见
Bye.
-警卫  -警卫去休息了
- Guard! - The guard is on a break.
-可能在跟老婆通话  -对  她怀孕了
- Probably talking to his wife. - Yeah, she's pregnant.
-是吗  -是啊
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah.
是啊
Yeah.
嗯
夜猴侠  对
Night Monkey. Yeah.
你们没事吧
You guys okay?
-不好意思  先生  -什么事
- Excuse me, sir? - Yeah?
-可以借你的电话吗  -嗯
- Could I borrow your phone? - Yeah.
这里的人都好好啊
Everyone is so nice here.
好吧
Okay.
好
接接接
Pick up, pick up, pick up.
我搞砸了  我需要个交通工具
I messed up. I need a... I need a ride.
我在哪  我在哪  先生
Where am I? Where am I, sir?
这里是布克普朗克戴克
It's Broek op Langedijk.
等等  可以冲这里说吗
Hang on. Could you say that into there?
这里是布克普朗克戴克
It's Broek op Langedijk here.
荷兰  布克普朗克戴克
好  不客气
Yeah, no problem.
谢谢
Thanks.
你听懂了吗
Did you get that?
彼得  你没事吧
Peter? Are you okay?
-哈皮  是你吗  -当然是我
- Happy, is that you? - Is it me? Yeah, of course it's me.
站住  告诉我一件只有你知道的事
Stop! Tell me something only you would know.
只有我知道
Only I would know.
记得我们去德国那次吗
Remember we went to Germany?
你在房间点了付费视频
You pay-per-viewed a video in your room?
他们虽没列出标题  但结账时
They didn't list titles, but I could tell by the price
我一看价钱就知道你看了成人电影
it was an adult film at the front destk.
-你还不知道我怎么发现的  -好吧
- And you didn't know how I knew... - Okay. Okay,
是你  别说了
fine! It's you. It's you. It's you. Stop.
见到你太好了
It's so good to see you.
彼得  你得告诉我出了什么事
Peter, you gotta tell me what the hell is going on here.
好  别动
Okay, hold still.
好了
There we go.
你不是有超级怪力吗
I thought you had super strength.
还是疼的
It still hurts.
-哈皮  拜托  -好了  放松
- Happy, come on. - All right, relax.
-就差几下了  好了  -天啊
- Just a few more. There we go. - Oh, my God.
-放松  -别叫我放松  哈皮
- Relax. - Don't tell me to relax, Happy!
我搞砸得这么严重怎么放松
How can I relax when I messed up so bad?
我信任了贝克
I trusted Beck. Right?
我当他是朋友
I thought he was my friend.
我把斯塔克先生留给我的唯一一件东西给了他
So, I gave him the only thing that Mr. Stark left behind for me,
他现在要杀了我朋友和半个欧洲
and now he's gonna kill my friends and half of Europe,
所以别叫我放松
so please do not tell me to relax.
抱歉  哈皮  抱歉  我不该喊的
I'm sorry, Happy. I'm sorry. I shouldn't shout.
我就是好想他
I just really miss him.
我也想他
Yeah, I miss him too.
不管我去哪
Everywhere I go...
都能看到他的脸
I see his face.
全世界都在问
And the whole world is asking
谁会做下一个钢铁侠
who's gonna be the next Iron Man... And
我不知道那是不是我  哈皮  我不是钢铁侠
I don't know if that's me, Happy. I'm not Iron Man.
你不是钢铁侠
You're not Iron Man.
你也不会成为钢铁侠
You're never gonna be Iron Man.
没人能达到托尼的境界
Nobody could live up to Tony.
托尼都不能
Not even Tony.
托尼是我最好的朋友
Tony was my best friend.
但他状态很糟
And he was a mess.
他总质疑自己做的一切
He second-guessed everything he did.
心里乱得很
He was all over the place.
他唯一没质疑过的抉择
The one thing that he did that he didn't second-guess
就是选你
was picking you.
我觉得托尼那么做
I don't think Tony would have done what he did
是因为他知道等他不在了
if he didn't know that you were gonna be here
你肯定会挺身而出
after he was gone.
你的朋友们有麻烦了
Now, your friends are in trouble,
你孤身一人  你的装备不见了
you're all alone, your tech is missing.
你打算怎么办
What are you gonna do about it?
我要去扁他
I'm gonna kick his ass.
我是指现在  我们具体要做什么
I mean, right now. Like specifically, what are we gonna do?
因为我们在一片郁金香花田上空
Because we've been hovering over a tulip field
悬停15分钟了
for the last 15 minutes.
好吧  我不能给我的朋友们打电话
Right. I can't call my friends
因为他在追踪他们的手机
because he's tracking their phones.
把你的手机给我
Give me your phone.
-我的手机吗  -对
- My cell phone? - Yeah.
好  给
Okay. Here.
你的密码是什么
What's your password?
"密码"
"Password."
不  你的密码是什么
No, what is your password?
"密码"这个词
"Password," Spelled out, password.
你作为安全主管
You're the head of security,
居然用"密码"做密码
and your password is "Password"?
我也挺不好意思的
I don't feel good about it either.
大家好  喝杯茶吗
Hello, governor. Cup of tea for you?
我马上到伦敦了
I'm gonna be in London soon.
-他们在伦敦  -伦敦  好
- They're in London. - London, okay.
我需要套战衣
Yeah, I need a suit.
战衣
Suit?
好
Okay, um...
调出关于蜘蛛侠的一切
bring up everything you have on Spider-Man.
打开那个  好  不不
Yeah, open that. Okay, no, no, no.
-怎么了  -没事
- What? - Nothing.
你搞定战衣  我来搞定音乐
You take care of the suit. I'll take care of the music.
我好喜欢齐柏林飞艇
I love Led Zeppelin.
好  调出我的射网器
Okay, can you pull up my web-shooters?
分离电击蛛网
Isolate the Taser webs,
重构  增加电压
and reconfigure and boost the voltage
增强25%
to a factor of 25 percent,
让我完全手控爆炸
and give me complete manual control over detonation.
我以为克里人的潜伏间谍
I thought Kree having sleeper cells
是绝密情报
was top secret information.
尼克  卫星监测到了电磁脉冲
Nick, satellites are picking up an EM pulse.
那事不是结束了吗
I thought that was over.
而且是最大的一波
It's the biggest one yet.
-在哪  -伦敦
- Where? - London.
好  各位  旅游公司组织了城市环游
Okay, guys, the company set up a city tour,
然后我们吃口饭  就去机场
and then we'll grab a bite and head to the airport.
没有人打算说说这一切多疯狂吗
Is no one else gonna acknowledge how crazy this is?
我懂  这趟科学出游
Oh, yeah, I get it. There's been nothing scientific
完全不科学
about this science tour at all.
不不  我是在说彼得
No, no, I'm talking about Peter.
难道没别人注意到他多可疑吗
Has no one else here noticed how shady he is?
因为我看到他只穿内裤跟个女人
Because I saw him in the back room of a rest stop
在一个休息站的后屋里
with some woman in his underwear,
而且他总偷偷溜走
and he's always sneaking away,
比如在歌剧院时
like back at the opera, huh?
现在他又突然离队
And, now what, he's suddenly off the trip,
去柏林找亲戚了
like with his family in Berlin?
难道没有别人想知道真相吗
Is no one else here interested in the truth?
"客观事实的概念
"The very concept of objective truth
都在从这世上消失"
is fading out of the world."
乔治·奥威尔  谢谢  MJ
George Orwell. Thank you, MJ.
是啊  既然彼得不在
Yeah. Well, I mean, since Peter's not really here
不能讲出他的事实
to tell his truth,
那你的事实呢  布拉德
what about you, Brad?
你为什么觉得你可以拍人上厕所的照片
Why do you think it's cool to take pictures of people in the bathroom?
是啊  哥们  那怎么回事
Yeah, dude, what's that about?
不不  不是那样的
No, no, no, it wasn't like that. It was...
我是想...
I was trying to take a...
我们忘记这一切的疯狂吧
Let's just put all this craziness behind us
度过一个美好平和的下午
and have a nice, peaceful afternoon.
"好啊  哈林顿老师"同学们说  好
"Sounds great, Mr. Harrington," Said the class. Okay.
我现在要做个酷老师
I'm gonna be a cool teacher right now.
你别再那么做了  是很奇怪
You gotta stop doing that. Okay? It is weird.
再不许在厕所里拍照了
No more photos in the bathroom.
不管是小便池还是隔间
Urinal or stalls.
-好吗  -看啊
- Okay? - Look at this.
哈林顿先生  这是你的大巴
Mr. Harrington, come on, this is your bus.
我们有自己的大巴呢
We got a bus all to ourselves.
见到你们很高兴  来吧
Nice to see you all. Come along.
-给我吧  好  -走吧  谢谢
- I'll get this, yeah? Why not? - Let's go. Thank you.
嗯  谢谢
Yeah. Thank you, brother.
好的
All right.
孩子们接到了
I have the kids.
我尽快赶过来了
I got here as fast as I could.
我把周边扫了一遍  没有发现
I did a full perimeter sweep. Nothing.
该死
Damn it.
脉冲在激增
Pulse is spiking.
我再去看看
I'll take another look.
你一看到什么  马上报告
Soon as you see something, report.
我们只剩你了  贝克
You're all we've got, Beck.
如果这是我担心的那样
If this is what I fear,
那上帝保佑我们了  弗瑞
then God help us, Fury.
上帝保佑我们所有人
God help us all.
好的  没有复仇者来  我们可以开始了
Okay, people, no Avengers coming. We're good to go.
-威廉  启动无人机  -收到  兄弟
- William, launch the drones. - Copy that, brother.
无人机进入大气层  武器就绪
Drones are entering the atmosphere weapons-hot.
-很好  詹妮丝  -还在熨斗篷呢
- Excellent. Janice? - Still working on the cape.
把褶子都熨平了
You gotta get those wrinkles out.
再过几小时  我真可能要跟女王握手了
In a few hours, I could literally be shaking hands with the queen.
-古特曼  -马上就位
- Guterman? - Almost in position.
-好  来吧  维多利亚  -增强脉冲
- Okay. Hit it, Victoria. - Increasing pulse.
不管是什么
Whatever this thing is,
它比之前的强100倍
it's 100 times bigger than the previous ones.
伊迪丝
Edith?
是  昆廷
Yes, Quentin.
我要处理的麻烦在哪
Show me my loose ends.
节目一开始
Once the show's going,
就等我命令执行击杀
execute the kill order on my command.
-收到  -好
- Copy. - All right.
节目开始
Start the show.
我们来拯救世界吧  各位
Let's save the world, people.
我不喜欢这情况  绝对有问题
I don't like this. Something's definitely up.
你现在是蛛友了  "蜘蛛侠的朋友"
You're an FOS now. "Friend of Spider-Man."
你得记住  保持冷静
And you have to remember, just stay calm.
内德  那看上去不妙
Ned, that doesn't look good.
但那是假的  所以不必担心
But it's fake, so, there's nothing to worry about.
孩子们进入击杀区了
And the kids are in the kill zone.
干得好  古特曼
Great work, Guterman.
-干什么  -我是哈皮  哈皮·霍根
- What? - Happy here. Happy Hogan here.
我知道  你有什么事
I know. What do you want?
斯塔克先生那边在整理东西
Over at Mr. Stark's, going through his belongings.
你似乎留下了一块冲浪板
Apparently there was a surfboard you left behind.
-什么  -那边的人说
- What? - People over there said
尼克·弗瑞不像冲浪的人
they didn't think Nick Fury was a surfer,
但我说"人不可貌相"
but I said, "Appearances can be deceiving."
不是我的  永远别再打这个号码了
It's not mine. And don't ever call this number again.
英国  多赛特海岸
好  弗瑞听懂暗语了
Okay. Fury's got the coded message.
-你的朋友在塔桥上  -好
- Your friends are at the Tower Bridge. - Okay.
你朋友说是伦敦桥  但我还是猜出来了
Your boy called it London Bridge, but I figured it out.
-我去接他们  好吗  -好
- I'm gonna go scoop them up, okay? - Yeah.
-我们快到了  -是啊
- We're close. - We're close.
-战衣怎么样了  -快好了
- How's the suit coming? - Almost done.
-很好  -等等
- Good. - Wait, wait.
你走之前  如果我出事了
Before you go, if something happens to me,
你可以把这个给MJ吗
could you please give this to MJ?
你能安全回来的  到时你自己给她
You are gonna make it back. You'll give it to her yourself.
-你行的  -我行的
- Okay? You got this. - I got this.
-跟我说一遍  -他们用的是幻景科技
- Walk me through it. - I know it's illusion tech, right?
我只需要进入幻景内部
All I do is get on the inside of the illusion,
我就能击垮它
then I can take it down,
找到他  而他只是个人
find him, and he's just a guy.
我可以把伊迪丝夺回来
So, I can take EDITH right back.
好  但上次  你被火车撞了
Right, but last time, you got hit by a train.
是的  但这次
True, but this time...
我怎么解释呢
How do I explain this?
我有种第六感
I have a sixth sense.
彼得一激灵
The Peter-tingle.
你是说那个吧
That's what you're talking about, right?
但现在不好使
It's not working, though.
我听说现在不好使了  是吧
I heard it wasn't working right now. Is it?
是好使的
It is working.
-我不知道好不好...  -好
- I don't know if it's working... - Good.
好  你有彼得一激灵  这就是你的计划
Okay. You got the Peter-tingle. That's the plan.
我去接你的朋友
I'm gonna go get your friends.
你让你的彼得一激灵重新上线
You get that Peter-tingle back online.
我行的
I got this. I got this.
闪电开始
Cue the lightning.
Cuing lightning.
先生  上面还安全吗
Sir, is it still safe on the top,
还是我们该下来
or should we all come down?
天啊
Oh, my.
大巴司机怎么说
What did the bus driver say?
大巴司机不见了
Bus driver's gone.
-什么  -去哪了
- What? - Where?
没事的  戴尔老师和我能控制局面
It's okay. Mr. Dell and I have it under control!
不  别把我拉进来
No. Don't drag me into this.
我已经尽力了  朱利亚斯
I'm doing my best, Julius!
-听着  -又是巫术
- Look... - Oh, the witches are back.
天啊  快下车
Oh, my God, get off the bus!
好  跟我来  孩子们
Okay, follow me, kids.
来  快走
Come on, let's go!
这才是复仇者级别的威胁呢
Now, that is an Avengers-level threat.
这边走
This way. This way!
-好  -天啊
- Okay. Okay. - Oh, my God!
-弗拉士  -跟着手走
- Flash! - Follow that hand.
这边走  跟我来
This way. Follow me.
这都不是真的
It's not real, it's not real!
我看可挺真的
Well, it looks pretty real to me!
跟我来  孩子们
Follow me, kids!
地  风  火  水  不
Earth, wind, fire, water. Oh, no.
他们合体了  就像超能战士
They joined forces like the Power Rangers.
-那是战神金刚  -什么
- You're thinking of Voltron. - Who?
你想的是战神金刚
Voltron! You're thinking of Voltron!
看  是神秘客
Hey, look, it's Mysterio!
他会救我们的
He's gonna save us!
等等  如果神秘客知道我们知道了
Wait, if Mysterio knows we know...
-我们就危险了  -对  他们也是
- Then we're in danger. - Yeah, and so are they.
我们走吧
We should go.
灭了那巫术
Kill that witch! Ba-bow!
这是为了我家人
This is for my family!
你该去安全的地方  弗瑞
You should get somewhere safe, Fury.
我觉得这事不会有好结局的
I don't see this ending well.
多谢你关心
I appreciate your concern,
但我绝不会丢下战友
but I never leave my men behind.
好  通讯检查  听到吗  孩子
All right, comms check. Can you hear me, kid?
能听到  就是外面有点吵
Yeah. I can. It's a little loud out here.
-新战衣不错  -谢谢
- I like the new suit. - Thanks.
彼得  你确定那不是真的吗
Peter, you sure that's not real?
嗯  但比我想的要大100倍
Yeah, it's just 100 times bigger than I expected.
还是原计划
Still the play?
我们得升高些
We need to get high enough
以确保贝克不会看到我
so Beck doesn't see me coming.
收到  粘住了
Copy. Stay sticky.
-哈皮  -孩子  怎么了
- Happy. - Yeah, kid. What is it?
我们得认真地谈谈你和我婶婶的事
We need to have a serious conversation about you and my aunt!
贝克  报告
Beck, report!
古特曼  我需要个回应
Guterman, I need a response.
快点  果决点
Something quick and decisive.
"是所有那些元素怪
"It's all the Elementals.
它们不知怎么融合成了..."
They're somehow merged into something..."
...成了别的东西  要强大得多
...into something else. Something more powerful.
它在汲取地球核心的能量
It's drawing energy from the Earth's core.
这太扯了
See, now, that's some bullshit.
那是...
Is that...?
做好万全准备
Be ready for anything.
好
Yeah.
不是真的  不是真的
It's not real, it's not real, it's not real!
太赞了
That's awesome.
威廉  有无人机脱离阵型了
William, I've got drones breaking formation.
可能是撞了鸟群  没事的
Maybe they hit a flock of birds. You're fine.
我要看里面什么情况  我要手动控制
I wanna see what's happening there, I'm taking manual control.
你看到什么了吗
Do you see anything?
看到了
Yeah.
我要杀了他
And I'm gonna kill him.
希望成功
I hope this works.
你在吗
You got me?
我罩你
I got you.
老板  幻景被破坏了
Boss, the illusion is coming apart.
我看到你了
I see you.
-伊迪丝  保护我  -收到
- EDITH, give me some protection. - Copy.
中止幻景  中止
Kill it. Just kill the illusion. Kill it.
不  不能中止  他们会看到的
No, I'm not gonna kill it. They'll see.
我要他们看到什么他们就会看到什么
They'll see what I want them to see!
-你还需要斗篷吗  -是的  詹妮丝
- Do you still need the cape? - Yes, Janice.
-我还要斗篷  -好了
- I still need the cape. - Done.
-威廉  渲染我的幻景战衣  -好  等等
- Now William render my illusion suit. - All right, hang on.
怪物里都是无人机  简直疯了
The monster was full of drones! It's crazy!
你在那里呢
There you are.
慢慢来
Easy.
那是谁
Who the hell is that?
-内德  -哈皮
- Ned! - Happy!
我得带你们离开
I gotta get you guys out of here!
-上飞机  -你是谁
- Get on the jet! - Who are you?
我跟蜘蛛侠共事  你们得上飞机
I work with Spider-Man. Okay? You gotta get on that jet.
你为蜘蛛侠工作
You work for Spider-Man?
是跟蜘蛛侠共事  不是为他工作
I work with Spider-Man, not for Spider-Man.
-新计划  进塔楼  -什么
- New plan. Into the Tower. - What?
哈皮  你没事吧
Happy, are you okay?
我们没事  去抓贝克
Yeah. We're okay. Just get Beck.
-伊迪丝  目标是蜘蛛侠  -收到
- EDITH, target Spider-Man. - Copy.
我自己杀那些孩子
I'll just kill the kids myself.
你们在这儿呢
There you are.
进王冠权杖密室
Into the Crown Jewels vault!
-好  快走  -快走
- Yeah, go, go, go! - Come on.
-快走  -进密室
- Go! - Into the vault!
墙有八英尺厚呢  进密室
The walls are 8 feet thick. Go into the vault!
-什么  -进密室  快去
- What? - Into the vault. Go!
找掩护
Take cover!
好
Okay.
行吗
Yeah?
不  不要
No. No.
我看到你了
I see you.
拿开那玩意
Get that thing out...
快走
Go!
美队怎么做到的
How does Cap do that?
哈皮  说话  告诉我你们还活着
Happy, say something, please, to let me know you're alive!
-我在  -哈皮  谢天谢地
- I'm here. I'm here. - Happy, thank God.
我为我们争取到了时间
I bought us some time,
但不多
but not much.
我想靠近贝克  但我无法摆脱这些无人机
I'm trying to get to Beck, but I can't shake these drones!
找到你了
Gotcha.
上去
Going up!
可算
Finally.
威廉  情况怎么样
William, how we doing?
幻景几乎重建完毕
Illusion almost back up.
我不知道你要怎么把这事圆回来
I don't know how you're gonna spin this.
好啊  没网了
Oh, great. No webs.
-我们要死了吗  -有我在没人会死的
- Are we gonna die? - Nobody dies on my watch.
我的人生都浪费在打电游上了
I wasted my life playing video games,
我们就要死了
and we're gonna die.
我有个假身份证
I have a fake ID,
可我都没用过
and I've never even used it.
我每天都发蠢视频  就希望大家喜欢我
I post stupid videos daily for people to like me.
要不是你的蠢视频
If it wasn't for those stupid videos,
蜘蛛侠就不可能找到你
Spider-Man would've never found you.
蜘蛛侠...关注我吗
Spider-Man...? Spider-Man follows me?
是我救了我们  各位
I saved us, guys.
如果你救了我们  那我们怎么还是要死了
If you saved us, then why are we about to die?
-MJ  -别说了
- MJ! - Stop it!
对不起
I'm sorry, okay?
我执迷于说真话
It's just, I'm obsessed with telling the truth
哪怕这伤了其他人的感情
even if it hurts other people's feelings.
我爱上了蜘蛛侠的婶婶
I'm in love with Spider-Man's aunt.
我们不是在分享心里话吗
We're sharing, right?
你的谎言结束了  贝克
Your lies are over, Beck.
这的确不理想  但我还有应急措施
This certainly isn't ideal, but I have contingencies.
伊迪丝
Edith?
把眼镜给我
Just give me the glasses.
你要这个吗
You want these?
来拿啊
Come and get them.
上线吧  彼得一激灵
Come on, Peter-tingle.
这些无人机怎么不开火
Why aren't these drones firing?
你处在射击范围内
You're in the strike zone.
-你可能被击中  -不
- The chance of getting hit is... - No,
所有无人机马上开火
fire all the drones now!
贝克
Beck!
Beck.
你骗了我
You lied to me.
我还信任了你
And I trusted you.
我知道
I know.
那是最...
That's the most...
让人失望的部分
d-disappointing part.
你是个好人  彼得
You're a good person, Peter.
真是个弱点
Such a weakness.
斯塔克是对的
Stark was right.
这是你应得的
You do deserve them.
你再骗不了我了
You can't trick me anymore.
伊迪丝  关闭无人机
EDITH, turn off the drones.
生物识别扫描完成  欢迎回来  彼得
Biometric scan complete. Welcome back, Peter.
是否执行全部取消协议
Shall I execute all cancellation protocols?
做吧
Just do it.
-全部执行  -确认
- Execute them all. - Confirmed.
矛给我
Give me the spear.
那是戟
That's a halberd.
谢谢
Thank you.
你怎么能做这么多坏事
How could you do all of this?
你会懂的  彼得
You'll see, Peter.
人们需要相信
People, they need to believe.
如今
And nowadays...
他们什么都肯信
they'll believe anything.
他...
Is he...?
这是真的吗
Is this real?
幻景都停止了  彼得
All illusions are down, Peter.
下载
太好了
Yeah!
你去哪
Where you going?
MJ
MJ.
-你没事吧  -我没事  你没事吧
- Are you okay? - I'm okay. Are you okay?
-嗯嗯  -其他人都没事吧
- Yeah. Yeah. - Is everybody else okay?
嗯  大家都没事
Yeah, everyone's okay.
-怎么回事  -无人机
- What happened? - There was just the drones,
它们本来跟着我们  然后突然就停了
and they were following us, and then they just stopped.
-是你停止了它们吗  -对
- Was that you? - Yeah.
你抓到他了吗
Did you get him?
-嗯  -我...
- Yeah. - Well, I, um...
带来了那个
brought that.
以防你还需要帮助
In case you needed some help.
谢谢
Thanks.
总之
Anyway, uh,
有个汗津津的家伙跟我们一起在塔楼里
there was this sweaty guy in the tower with us.
他好像是为你工作
I think he's like, works for you or something.
他...
He, um...
他给了我这个
He gave me this.
不不
No. No.
MJ  真抱歉
MJ, I'm so sorry.
-我有个计划的  很傻  -彼得
- I had this plan. I had this stupid plan. - Peter.
我都写下来了  我打算给你买下这个
I wrote it all down, and I was gonna buy you this
然后去巴黎送你  在...
and give it to you in Paris at the top...
你吻了我
And you kissed me.
-什么  -是啊
- What? What? - Yeah.
我在跟人亲近上
I don't really have much luck
不怎么走运
when it comes to getting close to people.
所以我撒谎了
So I lied.
我看你
I wasn't just watching you
不仅仅是因为我猜到你蜘蛛侠
because I thought you were Spider-Man.
太好了
That's great.
-黑色大丽花  就像拿起谋杀案  -谋杀案
- Black dahlia, like the murder. - The murder.
-好  -是啊
- Good. - Yeah.
抱歉都坏了
Sorry it's broken.
我更喜欢坏掉的
I actually like it better broken.
我真的好喜欢你
I really like you.
我也真的好喜欢你
I really like you too.
好  那我...
Okay. I should...
我回去找同学们了
I should probably get back to the class.
我去...
I'll go and...
-嗯  我也不知道  -好吧
- Yeah. Heh. I don't know. - Heh. Okay.
以防万一
Just in case.
不
Yeah, no.
不  梅  你是对的
No, May, you're right.
他干得很棒  他很坚强
He did great. He was strong.
对  我也很高兴他留下了
Yeah. I'm glad he stayed too.
我得挂了
I gotta go.
很高兴你还活着
Well, I'm glad you're alive.
看来那句暗语起作用了
I guess the coded message worked.
"人不可貌相"
"Appearances can be deceiving."
你怎么不直接冲镜头眨眼
I'm surprised you didn't just wink in the camera.
-你不是懂了  -那也是因为我一开始
- It worked. - Only because I had serious doubts
就对贝克持有很深的怀疑
about Beck from the beginning.
才不是  他完全信了
Not true. He had zero doubts.
帕克呢
Where's Parker?
他跟个姑娘在一起呢
He's with a girl.
我需要跟他谈谈
I need to speak with him.
他会联系你的
He'll call you.
他...
He'll...?
好啊  好
Okay. Great.
他最好联系我
Well, he better.
否则我拿你是问
Or it's your ass.
你可别想跟我玩消失
And don't even think about ghosting me.
新泽西  纽瓦克
你确定没有别人发现吗
Are you sure no one else has figured it out?
确定  反正也没别人注意你
Yeah, I mean, it's not like anybody really pays attention to you.
扎心
Ouch.
除了我
Except for me.
谢谢
Thanks.
-别迟到  -我不会的
- Don't be late. - I won't.
回见
See you later.
-你们好可爱  -谢谢
- You guys are so cute. - Thanks.
我还想  或许我们可以
I was thinking that maybe we should all,
比如说  一起去双人约会什么的
I don't know, like go on a double date or something.
我们分手了
We broke up.
不  怎么了  为什么
No. What? Why?
男人和女人会渐渐疏远
Men and women grow apart,
但他们所共同经历的旅程
but the journey they share together
将永远成为他们的一部分
will always be a part of them.
-你好睿智  -谢谢
- You are so wise. - Thank you.
你好  杰拉德
Hello, Gerald.
汤普森
妈妈不能来吗
Could Mother not make it?
-梅  -我保证...
- May! - I promise you...
他来了  别给我开罚单
He's here. Don't give me a ticket.
你没事太好了
I'm so glad you're okay.
真的  我没事  我真的很好
No, for real, I'm good. I'm actually really fine.
走吧  你的包呢
Let's go. Where are your bags?
对啊  被炸飞了
Oh, right. They got blown up.
是啊
Yeah.
我给你买了热奶油百吉饼
I got you hot buttered bagels.
-太谢谢了  -我了解你
- Thank you so much. - I know my boy.
这几年来  我一直保护着我的身份
I kept my identity pretty guarded this past couple years.
我面临了很多欺骗
I faced a lot of deception.
我厌倦了谎言
And I'm tired of the lies.
所以该说出实话了
So it's time for the truth to be out there.
你们在约会吗
Are you dating?
-是的  -不算
- Yes. - Not really.
-什么  -我们...
- What? - Well...
-我以为...  -夏季情缘吧
- I think... - Summer fling.
是啊  但发展深刻了
Yes, that evolves and grows like any other.
我还不确定会向什么方向发展
I still don't know where it's going to go.
不管发展到什么方向
Open to wherever it might lead.
都有可能
Anywhere.
-分分合合  -并把它分享给...
- On or off. - To share it with people...
不论怎样  我们永远是朋友
We'll always be friends, no matter what.
我还是走了  我还有约会
I'm gonna go because I've got a date.
我们都是紧密联系在一起的
...because we all are interconnected.
-再见  -是啊
- Bye. - We are.
抱歉
Sorry!
-就来  两分钟  -别边发短信边荡蛛丝
抱歉我迟到了
Sorry I'm late.
-没事  -你准备好了
- It's fine. - You ready?
-嗯  -你会喜欢这个的
- Yeah. - You're gonna love this.
好吧  好吧
Okay! Okay!
-好吧  -准备好了吗
- Okay. Okay. - You ready?
嗯  我不看  我不看了
Yeah. I'm just not gonna watch. I'm not gonna watch.
我还是闭眼吧
I should stop looking. I'm gonna stop looking!
蜘蛛侠：英雄远征
好了  把我放下吧
Okay. You can put me down now! You can put me down now!
你没事吧
You okay?
嗯  我没事
Yeah. Yeah, I'm okay.
但是我们再别那么干了
Let's just... Never, never doing that again.
-我再也不要试了  -好
- I'm never doing that again. - Okay.
我还是走了
I should probably get out of here.
-注意安全  -回见
- Be safe. - See you later.
这里是突发新闻
This is breaking news.
我们为您带来
We come to you now with
上周伦敦袭击的揭秘
revelations about last week's attack in London.
一个匿名消息源提供了这段视频
An anonymous source provided this video.
显示了昆廷·贝克  即神秘客
It shows Quentin Beck, aka Mysterio,
临死前的一幕
moments before his death.
警告各位  这段视频可能令人不安
A warning, you may find this video disturbing.
我成功把元素怪从维度裂缝送了回去
I managed to send the Elemental back through the dimensional rift,
但我恐怕不能活着离开这座桥了
but I don't think I'm gonna make it off this bridge alive.
不知为何  蜘蛛侠攻击了我
Spider-Man attacked me for some reason.
他有一支武器化无人机大军  斯塔克科技
He has an army of weaponized drones, Stark technology,
他说他是唯一有资格做新钢铁侠的人
he's saying he's the only one who's gonna be the new Iron Man.
别人都不行
No one else.
你确定要开始无人机袭击吗
Are you sure you want to commence the drone attack?
会造成严重人员伤亡
There will be significant casualties.
做吧  全部执行[杀死]
Do it. Execute them all.
这段惊人的视频于今天早些时候放出
This shocking video was released earlier today
发布于颇受争议的新闻网站
on the controversial news website
每日号角报网
TheDailyBugle.Net.
大家看到了  各位
There you have it, folks,
确凿证据  蜘蛛侠
conclusive proof that Spider-Man
残忍地杀害了神秘客
was responsible for the brutal murder of Mysterio,
这位跨维度战士
an interdimensional warrior
为保护我们星球献出了生命
who gave his life to protect our planet
他无疑将被历史铭记
and who will no doubt go down in history
为史上最伟大的超级英雄
as the greatest superhero of all time.
但还不止如此  各位
But that's not all, folks.
真正的爆炸新闻在这里
Here's the real blockbuster.
做好准备  你最好坐下
Brace yourselves. You might wanna sit down.
蜘蛛侠的真名...
Spider-Man's real... Spider-Man's real name is...
蜘蛛侠的真名是彼得·帕克
Spider-Man's name is Peter Parker.
搞什么...
What the fu...?
你得告诉他
You gotta tell him.
没事的
It was fine.
那小子处理好了
The little boy handled it.
我们也帮忙了
We helped.
-塔罗斯  -得了
- Talos. - Come off it.
我怎么可能知道
How was I supposed to know
整件事都是假的
that the whole thing was fake?
那都太像模像样了
I mean, that was all very, very convincing, you know.
表演  幻景
The performances, the illusion,
戏服  手工真不错
that costume, the craftsmanship in that.
这对于变形人来说太丢人了  好吧
I mean, this is just embarrassing for a shape-shifter. Fine.
你好  希望你的任务还顺利
Hey there. I hope your mission is going well.
我们一周前照你说的把眼镜给了帕克
We gave the glasses to Parker about a week ago, like you said.
场面很感人的
And it was very touching, you know?
真的很感人
Really, really quite touching.
塔罗斯
Talos.
在之后不久
And, you know, shortly after that,
一切都失控了
it really kind of went off the rails,
我们需要你回来
so we need you to come back.
因为大家都在问复仇者联盟在哪
Cause, everyone kept asking where the Avengers are,
我又不知道该怎么回答
I don't know what to say to that,
幸好蜘蛛侠赢...
so you're lucky that Spider-Man won...
都回去工作
Everybody back to work!
我的鞋谁拿了
Who's got my shoes?
缅怀感激斯坦·李和史蒂夫·迪特科